id,handle,text,is_retweet,time,lang,retweet_count,favorite_count,filtered_text,entities
780893126605037568,realDonaldTrump,"Join me for a 3pm rally - tomorrow at the Mid-America Center in Council Bluffs, Iowa! Tickets:… https://t.co/dfzsbICiXc",False,2016-09-27T22:13:24,en,2181,6172,"[('join', 1), ('pm', 1), ('rally', 1), ('tomorrow', 1), ('mid', 1)]","[('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('the Mid-America Center', 'FAC'), ('Council Bluffs', 'GPE'), ('Iowa', 'GPE')]"
780876760086880256,realDonaldTrump,"Once again, we will have a government of, by and for the people. Join the MOVEMENT today! https://t.co/lWjYDbPHav https://t.co/uYwJrtZkAe",False,2016-09-27T21:08:22,en,4132,11239,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('government', 1), ('people', 1), ('join', 1)]",[]
780867418012979204,realDonaldTrump,"On National #VoterRegistrationDay, make sure you're registered to vote so we can #MakeAmericaGreatAgain… https://t.co/0wib6UEZON",True,2016-09-27T20:31:14,en,2953,6963,"[('national', 1), ('voterregistrationday', 1), ('make', 1), ('sure', 1), ('registered', 1)]","[('#MakeAmericaGreatAgain', 'MONEY')]"
780863218646474757,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton's Campaign Continues To Make False Claims About Foundation Disclosure: 
https://t.co/zhkEfUouHH",False,2016-09-27T20:14:33,en,3833,9840,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('continues', 1), ('make', 1)]","[(""Hillary Clinton's"", 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/zhkEfUouHH', 'PERSON')]"
780861171238834176,realDonaldTrump,"'CNBC, Time magazine online polls say Donald Trump won the first presidential debate' via @WashTimes. #MAGA
https://t.co/PGimqYKPoJ",False,2016-09-27T20:06:25,en,4236,10948,"[('cnbc', 1), ('time', 1), ('magazine', 1), ('online', 1), ('poll', 1)]","[('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Time', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/PGimqYKPoJ', 'PERSON')]"
780859319319400448,realDonaldTrump,Great afternoon in Little Havana with Hispanic community leaders. Thank you for your support! #ImWithYou https://t.co/vxWZ2tyJTF,False,2016-09-27T19:59:04,en,4878,14110,"[('great', 1), ('afternoon', 1), ('little', 1), ('havana', 1), ('hispanic', 1)]","[('afternoon', 'TIME'), ('Little', 'GPE'), ('Havana', 'GPE'), ('Hispanic', 'NORP')]"
780853860135006211,realDonaldTrump,"In the last 24 hrs. we have raised over $13M from online donations and National Call Day, and we’re still going! Thank you America! #MAGA",False,2016-09-27T19:37:22,en,6939,23330,"[('last', 1), ('hr', 1), ('raised', 1), ('online', 1), ('donation', 1)]","[('the last 24', 'DATE'), ('National Call Day', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780826236213927937,realDonaldTrump,"Well, now they're saying that I not only won the NBC Presidential Forum, but last night the big debate. Nice!",False,2016-09-27T17:47:36,en,8534,28578,"[('well', 1), ('saying', 1), ('nbc', 1), ('presidential', 1), ('forum', 1)]","[('NBC', 'ORG'), ('last night', 'TIME')]"
780813996739981316,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you for your endorsement, @GovernorSununu. #MAGA 
https://t.co/8BEeQPsuyd",False,2016-09-27T16:58:58,en,4191,13152,"[('thank', 1), ('endorsement', 1), ('governorsununu', 1), ('maga', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('@GovernorSununu', 'PERSON'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780796008854876160,realDonaldTrump,"Such a great honor. Final debate polls are in - and the MOVEMENT wins!
#AmericaFirst #MAGA #ImWithYou… https://t.co/DV1BKMwHEM",False,2016-09-27T15:47:29,en,13576,27245,"[('great', 1), ('honor', 1), ('final', 1), ('debate', 1), ('poll', 1)]","[('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
780783037743267840,realDonaldTrump,'U.S. Murders Increased 10.8% in 2015' via @WSJ: https://t.co/CIJMQJhLqp,False,2016-09-27T14:55:57,en,5365,10729,"[('u', 1), ('murder', 1), ('increased', 1), ('via', 1), ('wsj', 1)]","[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('10.8%', 'PERCENT'), ('2015', 'DATE')]"
780781898071207940,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you! #TrumpWon #MAGA 
https://t.co/a5rr1i38km",False,2016-09-27T14:51:25,en,7255,17380,"[('thank', 1), ('trumpwon', 1), ('maga', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('TrumpWon', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780781327050235905,realDonaldTrump,Hillary's been failing for 30 years in not getting the job done - it will never change.,False,2016-09-27T14:49:09,en,12127,31856,"[('hillary', 1), ('failing', 1), ('year', 1), ('getting', 1), ('job', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('30 years', 'DATE')]"
780766220618436608,realDonaldTrump,'True blue-collar billionaire Donald Trump shows Hillary Clinton is out of touch' https://t.co/NHO1OicfVm,False,2016-09-27T13:49:07,en,5827,14338,"[('true', 1), ('blue', 1), ('collar', 1), ('billionaire', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
780758306239512577,realDonaldTrump,The #1 trend on Twitter right now is #TrumpWon - thank you!,False,2016-09-27T13:17:40,en,19561,52449,"[('trend', 1), ('twitter', 1), ('right', 1), ('trumpwon', 1), ('thank', 1)]","[('1', 'MONEY'), ('Twitter', 'PRODUCT'), ('TrumpWon', 'ORG')]"
780757611914391552,realDonaldTrump,I won every poll from last nights Presidential Debate - except for the little watched @CNN poll.,False,2016-09-27T13:14:55,en,9598,29309,"[('poll', 2), ('every', 1), ('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('presidential', 1)]","[('last nights', 'DATE'), ('@CNN', 'ORG')]"
780752731418009600,realDonaldTrump,"'How Trump won over a bar full of undecideds and Democrats'
https://t.co/WWO39kxn8Y",False,2016-09-27T12:55:31,en,6704,15988,"[('trump', 1), ('bar', 1), ('full', 1), ('undecideds', 1), ('democrat', 1)]","[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('https://t.co/WWO39kxn8Y', 'PERSON')]"
780752274020761601,realDonaldTrump,I really enjoyed the debate last night.Crooked Hillary says she is going to do so many things.Why hasn't she done them in her last 30 years?,False,2016-09-27T12:53:42,en,21628,59791,"[('last', 2), ('really', 1), ('enjoyed', 1), ('debate', 1), ('night', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('her last 30 years', 'DATE')]"
780719876335894528,realDonaldTrump,Great debate poll numbers - I will be on @foxandfriends at 7:00 to discuss. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-27T10:44:58,en,4437,16423,"[('great', 1), ('debate', 1), ('poll', 1), ('number', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1)]","[('7:00', 'TIME')]"
780656338628145153,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you! Four new #DebateNight polls with the MOVEMENT winning. Together, we will MAKE AMERICA SAFE &amp; GREAT AGAIN… https://t.co/39FCnUf8Pb",False,2016-09-27T06:32:29,en,10829,24078,"[('thank', 1), ('four', 1), ('new', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('poll', 1)]","[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT'), ('GREAT', 'GPE')]"
780646830090641408,realDonaldTrump,".@DRUDGE_REPORT's First Presidential Debate Poll:
Trump: 80%
Clinton: 20%
Join the MOVEMENT today &amp; lets #MAGA!… https://t.co/B12lgC97tn",False,2016-09-27T05:54:42,en,10763,24643,"[('drudge', 1), ('report', 1), ('first', 1), ('presidential', 1), ('debate', 1)]","[('First Presidential Debate Poll', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('80%', 'PERCENT'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('20%', 'PERCENT'), ('Join the MOVEMENT', 'PERSON'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780644145492877312,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you! CNBC #DebateNight poll with over 400,000 votes. 
Trump 61%
Clinton 39%
#AmericaFirst #ImWithYou… https://t.co/MJ3NwA98op",False,2016-09-27T05:44:02,en,16167,34480,"[('thank', 1), ('cnbc', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('poll', 1), ('vote', 1)]","[('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT'), ('400,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('61%', 'PERCENT'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('39%', 'PERCENT')]"
780642262921441280,realDonaldTrump,"TIME #DebateNight poll - over 800,000 votes. Thank you! 
#AmericaFirst #MAGA https://t.co/bTPX9E0wKu",False,2016-09-27T05:36:33,en,12479,27258,"[('time', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('poll', 1), ('vote', 1), ('thank', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT'), ('800,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780637633890451456,realDonaldTrump,".@newtgingrich just said ""a historic victory for Trump."" NICE!",False,2016-09-27T05:18:10,en,7709,24434,"[('newtgingrich', 1), ('said', 1), ('historic', 1), ('victory', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
780626558176333824,realDonaldTrump,"Wow, did great in the debate polls (except for @CNN - which I don't watch). Thank you!",False,2016-09-27T04:34:09,en,12739,40321,"[('wow', 1), ('great', 1), ('debate', 1), ('poll', 1), ('except', 1)]",[]
780618680338178048,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Governor @TerryBranstad! 
#AmericaFirst #Debates2016 https://t.co/yIeZctdQy8",False,2016-09-27T04:02:51,en,5578,14830,"[('thank', 1), ('governor', 1), ('terrybranstad', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('debate', 1)]",[]
780618351601192960,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Governor @Mike_Pence!
Lets MAKE AMERICA SAFE AND GREAT AGAIN with the American people. 
#AmericaFirst… https://t.co/6k7qP9X8nC",False,2016-09-27T04:01:32,en,7350,22113,"[('thank', 1), ('governor', 1), ('mike', 1), ('penny', 1), ('let', 1)]","[('American', 'NORP'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
780617562476441601,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Senator @TedCruz!
#Debates2016 #MAGA https://t.co/cgO6109USJ",False,2016-09-27T03:58:24,en,18519,39447,"[('thank', 1), ('senator', 1), ('tedcruz', 1), ('debate', 1), ('maga', 1)]","[('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780598541441912832,realDonaldTrump,".@HillaryClinton’s Nuclear Agreement Paved The Way For The $400 Million Ransom Payment #DebateNight
https://t.co/qfZTx6aKYs",False,2016-09-27T02:42:49,en,8575,19522,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('nuclear', 1), ('agreement', 1), ('paved', 1), ('way', 1)]","[('$400 Million', 'MONEY'), ('DebateNight', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/qfZTx6aKYs', 'PERSON')]"
780597941979480064,realDonaldTrump,Nothing on emails. Nothing on the corrupt Clinton Foundation. And nothing on #Benghazi. #Debates2016 #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T02:40:26,en,30921,56562,"[('nothing', 3), ('email', 1), ('corrupt', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('foundation', 1)]","[('Clinton Foundation', 'ORG')]"
780596871102201856,realDonaldTrump,.@HillaryClinton - Obama #ISIS Strategy Has Allowed It To Expand To Become A Global Threat #DebateNight https://t.co/f7PctDE31L,False,2016-09-27T02:36:11,en,6680,15499,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('obama', 1), ('isi', 1), ('strategy', 1), ('allowed', 1)]",[]
780596317865254913,realDonaldTrump,.@realDonaldTrump calling out @HillaryClinton's support for NAFTA = most searched moment during tonight's debate.… https://t.co/2BovwrJisi,True,2016-09-27T02:33:59,en,6139,13209,"[('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('calling', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('support', 1), ('nafta', 1)]","[('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON'), ('NAFTA', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780594918616162304,realDonaldTrump,"Russia has more warheads than ever, N Korea is testing nukes, and Iran got a sweetheart deal to keep theirs. Thanks, @HillaryClinton.",False,2016-09-27T02:28:26,en,11851,26791,"[('russia', 1), ('warhead', 1), ('ever', 1), ('n', 1), ('korea', 1)]","[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('N Korea', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON')]"
780594362862362624,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton failed all over the world. 
❌LIBYA
❌SYRIA
❌IRAN
❌IRAQ
❌ASIA PIVOT
❌RUSSIAN RESET
❌BENGHAZI… https://t.co/OoakXs2rij",False,2016-09-27T02:26:13,en,21745,40457,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('failed', 1), ('world', 1), ('libya', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('❌', 'GPE'), ('SYRIA', 'ORG'), ('IRAN', 'ORG'), ('❌', 'GPE'), ('IRAQ', 'GPE'), ('ASIA PIVOT', 'ORG'), ('❌BENGHAZI', 'PERSON')]"
780593350604824576,realDonaldTrump,"100% TRUE --&gt; @realDonaldTrump is right - @HillaryClinton did call TPP ‘the gold standard’ #Debates2016 
https://t.co/W7L7a9wSCB",True,2016-09-27T02:22:12,en,7419,12728,"[('true', 1), ('gt', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('right', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1)]","[('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('TPP', 'ORG')]"
780593298247483392,realDonaldTrump,Hillary Clinton is the only candidate on stage who voted for the Iraq War. #Debates2016 #MAGA https://t.co/Um5WJXEEKr,False,2016-09-27T02:21:59,en,9001,20725,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('stage', 1), ('voted', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('the Iraq War', 'EVENT'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780592744355893248,realDonaldTrump,".@HillaryClinton's 2008 Campaign And Supporters Trafficked In Rumors About Obama's Heritage #DebateNight 
https://t.co/6EEOAaCiNv",False,2016-09-27T02:19:47,en,5763,12471,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('supporter', 1), ('trafficked', 1), ('rumor', 1)]",[]
780592630585499648,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary's policies have made America less safe, that's why 200+ general and military leaders have endorsed… https://t.co/x7sBpy0CEV",True,2016-09-27T02:19:20,en,4741,10739,"[('hillary', 1), ('policy', 1), ('made', 1), ('america', 1), ('le', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('200', 'CARDINAL')]"
780590406501150723,realDonaldTrump,"Jesse Jackson on @realDonaldTrump - when he donated space for the Rainbow/Push Coalition. 
#DebateNight https://t.co/JTbqO0DNzy",True,2016-09-27T02:10:30,en,5055,8520,"[('jesse', 1), ('jackson', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('donated', 1), ('space', 1)]","[('Jesse Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('the Rainbow/Push Coalition', 'ORG'), ('DebateNight https://t.co/JTbqO0DNzy', 'PRODUCT')]"
780585742850555904,realDonaldTrump,I will stand with police and protect ALL Americans! #Debates2016 #MAGA https://t.co/CX4oEWgEMp,False,2016-09-27T01:51:58,en,12173,33572,"[('stand', 1), ('police', 1), ('protect', 1), ('american', 1), ('debate', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
780585254583169078,realDonaldTrump,"When @realDonaldTrump is POTUS, families are going to be safe and secure. Law and order will be RESTORED! #MAGA… https://t.co/4Qo9gV7mgc",True,2016-09-27T01:50:01,en,4550,11239,"[('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('potus', 1), ('family', 1), ('going', 1), ('safe', 1)]","[('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('RESTORED', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/4Qo9gV7mgc', 'PERSON')]"
780583741051768832,realDonaldTrump,WATCH: @realDonaldTrump on the stakes in this election #Debates2016 https://t.co/l7DSbPXDGh,True,2016-09-27T01:44:01,en,1936,5930,"[('watch', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('stake', 1), ('election', 1), ('debate', 1)]",[]
780581933176778752,realDonaldTrump,"This is the simple fact about @HillaryClinton: she is a typical politician - all talk, no action. #Debates2016",False,2016-09-27T01:36:50,en,13308,32127,"[('simple', 1), ('fact', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('typical', 1), ('politician', 1)]","[('Debates2016', 'MONEY')]"
780581215820591104,realDonaldTrump,HILLARY'S BAD TAX HABIT! https://t.co/x3FBy8Hdq2,False,2016-09-27T01:33:59,en,11774,21663,"[('hillary', 1), ('bad', 1), ('tax', 1), ('habit', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('HILLARY', 'PERSON')]"
780580825234415616,realDonaldTrump,A Clinton economy = more taxes and more spending! #DebateNight https://t.co/oFlaAhrwe5,False,2016-09-27T01:32:25,en,7878,16568,"[('clinton', 1), ('economy', 1), ('tax', 1), ('spending', 1), ('debatenight', 1)]","[('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780579923295600640,realDonaldTrump,.@HillaryClinton has been part of the rigged DC system for 30 years? Why would we take policy advice from her? #Debates2016,False,2016-09-27T01:28:50,en,9707,22634,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('part', 1), ('rigged', 1), ('dc', 1), ('system', 1)]","[('DC', 'GPE'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Debates2016', 'MONEY')]"
780579728964980736,realDonaldTrump,"Instead of driving jobs and wealth away, AMERICA will become the world's great magnet for innovation and job creati… https://t.co/02NMQn3ZNQ",False,2016-09-27T01:28:04,en,7189,19174,"[('job', 2), ('instead', 1), ('driving', 1), ('wealth', 1), ('away', 1)]","[('AMERICA', 'GPE')]"
780578636294459392,realDonaldTrump,.@HillaryClinton channels John Kerry on trade: she was for bad trade deals before she was against them. #TPP #Debates2016,False,2016-09-27T01:23:43,en,5045,13196,"[('trade', 2), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('channel', 1), ('john', 1), ('kerry', 1)]","[('John Kerry', 'PERSON'), ('Debates2016', 'MONEY')]"
780577426657120258,realDonaldTrump,.@HillaryClinton and Obama policies increased debt by $9trillion over the last 8 years,False,2016-09-27T01:18:55,en,7836,17385,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('obama', 1), ('policy', 1), ('increased', 1), ('debt', 1)]","[('9trillion', 'MONEY'), ('the last 8 years', 'DATE')]"
780576225848885249,realDonaldTrump,A @realDonaldTrump Administration will bring JOBS BACK! #Debates2016 https://t.co/4O3rIyycyW,True,2016-09-27T01:14:09,en,3928,8756,"[('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('administration', 1), ('bring', 1), ('job', 1), ('back', 1)]","[('Debates2016', 'MONEY')]"
780569413321789440,realDonaldTrump,"Why isn't Hillary Clinton 50 points ahead?
#DebateNight https://t.co/iux7icIkaT",False,2016-09-27T00:47:05,en,16770,31043,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('point', 1), ('ahead', 1), ('debatenight', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'ORG')]"
780550185365737472,realDonaldTrump,Join @realDonaldTrump on his official social media platforms during tonight's debate ~ as @TeamTrump manages rapid… https://t.co/hheOvJjvcZ,True,2016-09-26T23:30:40,en,3532,8312,"[('join', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('official', 1), ('social', 1), ('medium', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780535389853458432,realDonaldTrump,"My team of deplorables will be managing my Twitter account for this evenings debate. Tune in!
#DebateNight #TrumpPence16",False,2016-09-26T22:31:53,en,19836,57971,"[('team', 1), ('deplorables', 1), ('managing', 1), ('twitter', 1), ('account', 1)]","[('Twitter', 'PRODUCT')]"
780444199737036800,realDonaldTrump,"#Polls showing @realDonaldTrump surging, @hillaryclinton #slipping, have HER camp on defense/lowering expectations, going into #Debates2016",True,2016-09-26T16:29:31,en,7925,18329,"[('poll', 1), ('showing', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('surging', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1)]","[('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('Debates2016', 'MONEY')]"
780377077518364673,realDonaldTrump,"New national Bloomberg poll just released - thank you! Join the MOVEMENT: https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW. 
#TrumpTrain… https://t.co/xDGCwYVK0Q",False,2016-09-26T12:02:48,en,11472,28638,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('new', 1), ('national', 1), ('bloomberg', 1)]","[('Bloomberg', 'GPE'), ('https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW.', 'ORG'), ('TrumpTrain', 'MONEY')]"
780213717082529792,realDonaldTrump,"Really sad news: The great Arnold Palmer, the ""King,"" has died. There was no-one like him - a true champion! He will be truly missed.",False,2016-09-26T01:13:40,en,17061,60847,"[('really', 1), ('sad', 1), ('news', 1), ('great', 1), ('arnold', 1)]","[('Arnold Palmer', 'PERSON')]"
780199873979219968,realDonaldTrump,Five people killed in Washington State by a Middle Eastern immigrant. Many people died this weekend in Ohio from drug overdoses. N.C. riots!,False,2016-09-26T00:18:40,en,11289,29909,"[('people', 2), ('five', 1), ('killed', 1), ('washington', 1), ('state', 1)]","[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Washington State', 'GPE'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('N.C.', 'GPE')]"
https://t.co/VHuyE65hgi https://t.co/6KDPrQxSED",False,2016-09-25T18:15:11,en,11555,30493,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('readout', 1), ('meeting', 1), ('israeli', 1)]","[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
780034352604405760,realDonaldTrump,Looking forward to my meeting with Benjamin Netanyahu in Trump Tower at 10:00 A.M.,False,2016-09-25T13:20:56,en,8533,31212,"[('looking', 1), ('forward', 1), ('meeting', 1), ('benjamin', 1), ('netanyahu', 1)]","[('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Trump Tower', 'FAC'), ('10:00 A.M.', 'TIME')]"
780030282854432768,realDonaldTrump,Bernie Sanders gave Hillary the Dem nomination when he gave up on the e-mails. That issue has only gotten bigger!,False,2016-09-25T13:04:46,en,8490,26708,"[('gave', 2), ('bernie', 1), ('sander', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('dem', 1)]","[('Bernie Sanders', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Dem', 'NORP')]"
780021651962462208,realDonaldTrump,"Many on the team and staff of Bernie Sanders have been treated badly by the Hillary Clinton campaign - and they like Trump on trade, a lot!",False,2016-09-25T12:30:28,en,8572,28770,"[('many', 1), ('team', 1), ('staff', 1), ('bernie', 1), ('sander', 1)]","[('Bernie Sanders', 'ORG'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
779827513375780864,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Roanoke, Virginia - this a MOVEMENT - join us today!
Sign up: https://t.co/NQEgRxQN2m
#AmericaFirst… https://t.co/Rz3DkpBQJu",False,2016-09-24T23:39:02,en,6424,20699,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('roanoke', 1), ('virginia', 1)]","[('Roanoke', 'ORG'), ('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('https://t.co/NQEgRxQN2', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
779729180334387200,realDonaldTrump,"If dopey Mark Cuban of failed Benefactor fame wants to sit in the front row, perhaps I will put Gennifer Flowers right alongside of him!",False,2016-09-24T17:08:17,en,31655,67133,"[('dopey', 1), ('mark', 1), ('cuban', 1), ('failed', 1), ('benefactor', 1)]","[('Mark Cuban', 'PERSON'), ('Benefactor', 'GPE'), ('Gennifer Flowers', 'PERSON')]"
779684468814667777,realDonaldTrump,Will be back in Virginia tonight- for a 6pm rally at the Berglund Center in Roanoke. Join me! Tickets:… https://t.co/6pQMSgPWuN,False,2016-09-24T14:10:37,en,4765,16323,"[('back', 1), ('virginia', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('pm', 1), ('rally', 1)]","[('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Berglund Center', 'FAC')]"
779662636770353152,realDonaldTrump,"""@KellyannePolls: Trump is headed for a win, says professor who has predicted 30 years of presidential outcomes   https://t.co/68WEMcuHSO""",False,2016-09-24T12:43:52,en,10001,24962,"[('kellyannepolls', 1), ('trump', 1), ('headed', 1), ('win', 1), ('say', 1)]","[('30 years', 'DATE')]"
779660413000617985,realDonaldTrump,The @SenTedCruz endorsement was a wonderful surprise. I greatly appreciate his support! We will have a tremendous victory on November 8th.,False,2016-09-24T12:35:02,en,12658,43068,"[('sentedcruz', 1), ('endorsement', 1), ('wonderful', 1), ('surprise', 1), ('greatly', 1)]","[('November 8th', 'DATE')]"
779638140810194944,realDonaldTrump,Today is the day! Knock on doors and make calls with us on National Day of Action! #TrumpTrain #MAGA… https://t.co/4iW06ROvsT,False,2016-09-24T11:06:32,en,7006,19238,"[('day', 2), ('today', 1), ('knock', 1), ('door', 1), ('make', 1)]","[('Today', 'DATE'), ('National Day of Action', 'EVENT'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
779503099492831233,realDonaldTrump,"Crooked Hillary's bad judgement forced her to announce that she would go to Charlotte on Saturday to grandstand. Dem pols said no way, dumb!",False,2016-09-24T02:09:56,en,9338,28604,"[('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('bad', 1), ('judgement', 1), ('forced', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Charlotte', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Dem', 'NORP')]"
779413482882162688,realDonaldTrump,"Join me in Roanoke, Virginia tomorrow at the Berglund Center- Coliseum ~ 6pm! Tickets available at:… https://t.co/bnEE6NX41Z",False,2016-09-23T20:13:49,en,4525,13490,"[('join', 1), ('roanoke', 1), ('virginia', 1), ('tomorrow', 1), ('berglund', 1)]","[('Roanoke', 'ORG'), ('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('the Berglund Center- Coliseum', 'ORG')]"
779372844513947648,realDonaldTrump,"'How Trump Would Stimulate the U.S. Economy'
https://t.co/jU3HHglnIu",False,2016-09-23T17:32:20,en,7058,16194,"[('trump', 1), ('would', 1), ('stimulate', 1), ('u', 1), ('economy', 1)]","[(""the U.S. Economy'"", 'ORG')]"
779371482329837568,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton just lost every Republican she ever had, including Never Trump, all farmers &amp; sm. biz, by saying she’ll tax estates at 65%.",False,2016-09-23T17:26:56,en,19788,40480,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('lost', 1), ('every', 1), ('republican', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Never Trump', 'FAC'), ('65%', 'PERCENT')]"
779349049778601984,realDonaldTrump,Tomorrow's the day! Knock on doors and make calls with us on National Day of Action! #TrumpTrain #MAGA… https://t.co/05NY0wJHkL,False,2016-09-23T15:57:47,en,6200,16518,"[('day', 2), ('tomorrow', 1), ('knock', 1), ('door', 1), ('make', 1)]","[('Tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('National Day of Action', 'EVENT'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
779348578040963073,realDonaldTrump,EXCLUSIVE: How Donald Trump's 30 million followers are crashing the Internet https://t.co/hV2z4yrTU7 https://t.co/lWkjmdyQ7Q,True,2016-09-23T15:55:55,en,6331,12874,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('exclusive', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[(""Donald Trump's"", 'PERSON'), ('30 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
779140534753435648,realDonaldTrump,Spoke with Governor @PatMcCroryNC of North Carolina today. He is doing a tremendous job under tough circumstances.,False,2016-09-23T02:09:13,en,8307,27919,"[('spoke', 1), ('governor', 1), ('patmccrorync', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1)]","[('Spoke', 'ORG'), ('North Carolina', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
779127602988650498,realDonaldTrump,"This is more than a campaign- it is a movement. #MakeAmericaGreatAgain
SIGN UP TODAY &amp; WE WILL WIN! https://t.co/2XBs5SSRC3",False,2016-09-23T01:17:50,en,6208,18880,"[('campaign', 1), ('movement', 1), ('makeamericagreatagain', 1), ('sign', 1), ('today', 1)]","[('SIGN UP', 'ORG'), ('TODAY &', 'ORG')]"
778968533749338112,realDonaldTrump,"Join me in Roanoke, Virginia on Saturday evening at 6pm! #MAGA
https://t.co/uKG55Pznwu",False,2016-09-22T14:45:45,en,4450,13782,"[('join', 1), ('roanoke', 1), ('virginia', 1), ('saturday', 1), ('evening', 1)]","[('Roanoke', 'ORG'), ('Virginia', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('evening', 'TIME'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
778912230633005056,realDonaldTrump,Will be on @foxandfriends now.,False,2016-09-22T11:02:01,en,2285,12885,"[('foxandfriends', 1)]",[]
778760237629210624,realDonaldTrump,"I will be interviewed from Cleveland, Ohio, on @seanhannity - Tonight at 10:00 P.M. Enjoy!",False,2016-09-22T00:58:03,en,3927,14775,"[('interviewed', 1), ('cleveland', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('seanhannity', 1), ('tonight', 1)]","[('Cleveland', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('10:00 P.M. Enjoy', 'TIME')]"
778759324491538432,realDonaldTrump,"""@ThAllenSBoucher: @DiamondandSilk @realDonaldTrump @seanhannity I love those beautiful gals."" D + S = Two amazing women!",False,2016-09-22T00:54:26,en,4586,16046,"[('thallensboucher', 1), ('diamondandsilk', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('seanhannity', 1), ('love', 1)]","[('Two', 'CARDINAL')]"
778758058394738689,realDonaldTrump,.@YoungDems4Trump  Thank you!,False,2016-09-22T00:49:24,en,3241,13612,"[('youngdems', 1), ('trump', 1), ('thank', 1)]",[]
778724315244040194,realDonaldTrump,"Great new polls! Thank you Nevada, North Carolina &amp; Ohio. Join the MOVEMENT today &amp; lets #MAGA!… https://t.co/Y8Sb8MNyXA",False,2016-09-21T22:35:19,en,10434,27350,"[('amp', 2), ('great', 1), ('new', 1), ('poll', 1), ('thank', 1)]","[('Nevada', 'GPE'), ('North Carolina &', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
778701067588472832,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Toledo, Ohio! It is so important for you to get out and VOTE on November 8, 2016! Lets MAKE AMERICA SAFE… https://t.co/MQdp4GgLIE",False,2016-09-21T21:02:56,en,8867,28193,"[('thank', 1), ('toledo', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('important', 1), ('get', 1)]","[('Toledo', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('VOTE', 'ORG'), ('November 8, 2016', 'DATE')]"
778655495037091845,realDonaldTrump,"WATCH: @IvankaTrump on ""women who work;"" empowering campaign celebrates modern women.  https://t.co/rMFe9o6WcL",True,2016-09-21T18:01:51,en,6947,15799,"[('woman', 2), ('watch', 1), ('ivankatrump', 1), ('work', 1), ('empowering', 1)]",[]
778585375174451200,realDonaldTrump,"Hopefully the violence &amp; unrest in Charlotte will come to an immediate end. To those injured, get well soon. We need unity &amp; leadership.",False,2016-09-21T13:23:13,en,13402,39218,"[('amp', 2), ('hopefully', 1), ('violence', 1), ('unrest', 1), ('charlotte', 1)]","[('Charlotte', 'GPE')]"
778584630396129281,realDonaldTrump,The situations in Tulsa and Charlotte are tragic. We must come together to make America safe again.,False,2016-09-21T13:20:15,en,9644,28498,"[('situation', 1), ('tulsa', 1), ('charlotte', 1), ('tragic', 1), ('must', 1)]","[('Tulsa', 'GPE'), ('Charlotte', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
778553790568001540,realDonaldTrump,"It is a MOVEMENT - not a campaign. Leaving the past behind, changing our future. Together, we will MAKE AMERICA SAF… https://t.co/Lt2L3NKzyi",False,2016-09-21T11:17:43,en,16408,41498,"[('movement', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('leaving', 1), ('past', 1), ('behind', 1)]","[('SAF', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/Lt2L3NKzyi', 'ORG')]"
778385212505989120,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Kenansville, North Carolina! Remember- on November 8th, that special interest gravy train is coming to a… https://t.co/AysJRMzvKw",False,2016-09-21T00:07:51,en,8131,24864,"[('thank', 1), ('kenansville', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1), ('remember', 1)]","[('Kenansville', 'GPE'), ('North Carolina', 'GPE'), ('November 8th', 'DATE')]"
778331181083418624,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you High Point, NC! I will fight for every neglected part of this nation &amp; I will fight to bring us together… https://t.co/DSaUpSptBz",False,2016-09-20T20:33:08,en,9574,28469,"[('fight', 2), ('thank', 1), ('high', 1), ('point', 1), ('nc', 1)]","[('NC', 'GPE')]"
778238281196662784,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton is taking the day off again, she needs the rest. Sleep well Hillary - see you at the debate!",False,2016-09-20T14:23:59,en,31049,76291,"[('hillary', 2), ('clinton', 1), ('taking', 1), ('day', 1), ('need', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778237787355111424,realDonaldTrump,Heading to North Carolina for two big rallies. Will be there soon. We will bring jobs back where they belong!,False,2016-09-20T14:22:02,en,6508,24283,"[('heading', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1), ('two', 1), ('big', 1)]","[('North Carolina', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
778237485402980352,realDonaldTrump,Do people notice Hillary is copying my airplane rallies - she puts the plane behind her like I have been doing from the beginning.,False,2016-09-20T14:20:50,en,12389,40362,"[('people', 1), ('notice', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('copying', 1), ('airplane', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778229963216519168,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Nevada! #AmericaFirst
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain 
https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW https://t.co/RJqHgq2Rn0",False,2016-09-20T13:50:56,en,5987,17783,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('nevada', 1), ('americafirst', 1)]","[('Nevada', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
778229686769967104,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Georgia! #AmericaFirst
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain 
https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW https://t.co/y01qpON7h7",False,2016-09-20T13:49:50,en,5816,17255,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('georgia', 1), ('americafirst', 1)]","[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
778202693215068161,realDonaldTrump,"Crooked Hillary has been fighting ISIS, or whatever she has been doing, for years. Now she has new ideas. It is time for change.",False,2016-09-20T12:02:35,en,9376,28160,"[('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('fighting', 1), ('isi', 1), ('whatever', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('ISIS', 'ORG'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
778027605572329472,realDonaldTrump,Amazing rally in Florida - this is a MOVEMENT! Join us today at https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW. https://t.co/BF1IqPXNho,False,2016-09-20T00:26:50,en,8269,22873,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('amazing', 1), ('rally', 1), ('florida', 1)]","[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW. https://t.co/BF1IqPXNho', 'ORG')]"
778025630956912640,realDonaldTrump,"Together, we will MAKE AMERICA SAFE AND GREAT AGAIN! #ImWithYou #AmericaFirst https://t.co/XhwUGw0v2H",False,2016-09-20T00:19:00,en,10580,28035,"[('together', 1), ('make', 1), ('america', 1), ('safe', 1), ('great', 1)]","[('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
778024608733749249,realDonaldTrump,"I will be interviewed on the @oreillyfactor - tonight from Florida, now. Enjoy!",False,2016-09-20T00:14:56,en,2820,13558,"[('interviewed', 1), ('oreillyfactor', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('florida', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
777958440211771392,realDonaldTrump,Philly FOP Chief On Presidential Endorsement: Clinton ‘Blew The Police Off' https://t.co/ATBY343pS1,False,2016-09-19T19:52:00,en,8020,17657,"[('philly', 1), ('fop', 1), ('chief', 1), ('presidential', 1), ('endorsement', 1)]",[]
777913567676866560,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton's weakness while she was Secretary of State, has emboldened terrorists all over the world..cont: https://t.co/E5BdTiwlur",False,2016-09-19T16:53:42,en,10464,25524,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('weakness', 1), ('secretary', 1), ('state', 1)]","[(""Hillary Clinton's"", 'PERSON'), ('State', 'ORG')]"
777910435425226753,realDonaldTrump,Once again someone we were told is ok turns out to be a terrorist who wants to destroy our country &amp; its people- how did he get thru system?,False,2016-09-19T16:41:15,en,16143,42166,"[('someone', 1), ('told', 1), ('ok', 1), ('turn', 1), ('terrorist', 1)]",[]
777908242538196992,realDonaldTrump,"Great job once again by law enforcement! We are proud of them and should embrace them - without them, we don't have a country!",False,2016-09-19T16:32:32,en,16413,49182,"[('great', 1), ('job', 1), ('law', 1), ('enforcement', 1), ('proud', 1)]",[]
777846568741441536,realDonaldTrump,"""@TarukMatuk: @CNN @FoxNews @realDonaldTrump @RogerRice10 Refugees from Syria over 10k plus more coming. Lots young males, poorly vetted.",False,2016-09-19T12:27:28,en,7735,18554,"[('tarukmatuk', 1), ('cnn', 1), ('foxnews', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('rogerrice', 1)]","[('@TarukMatuk', 'ORG'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('10k', 'DATE')]"
777843428449251328,realDonaldTrump,"""@AngPiazza: @foxandfriends  @realDonaldTrump he's the ONLY candidate that will keep us safe!""",False,2016-09-19T12:14:59,en,4585,15258,"[('angpiazza', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('keep', 1)]",[]
777825186758418432,realDonaldTrump,Will be on @foxandfriends at 7:02 A.M.  Enjoy.,False,2016-09-19T11:02:30,en,2153,11463,"[('foxandfriends', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('7:02 A.M.  ', 'TIME'), ('Enjoy', 'GPE')]"
777696726933180416,realDonaldTrump,"Terrible attacks in NY, NJ and MN this weekend. Thinking of victims, their families and all Americans! We need to be strong!",False,2016-09-19T02:32:03,en,12651,40764,"[('terrible', 1), ('attack', 1), ('ny', 1), ('nj', 1), ('mn', 1)]","[('NJ', 'ORG'), ('MN', 'ORG'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
777696356211326976,realDonaldTrump,"Under the leadership of Obama &amp; Clinton, Americans have experienced more attacks at home than victories abroad. Time to change the playbook!",False,2016-09-19T02:30:34,en,19662,49063,"[('leadership', 1), ('obama', 1), ('amp', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('american', 1)]","[('Obama &amp', 'ORG'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
777616135856545792,realDonaldTrump,HAPPY BIRTHDAY - to the United States Air Force!! https://t.co/5Gwi1M5R2t,False,2016-09-18T21:11:48,en,11885,34279,"[('happy', 1), ('birthday', 1), ('united', 1), ('state', 1), ('air', 1)]","[('the United States Air Force', 'GPE')]"
777614946951696384,realDonaldTrump,more media #polls showing @realDonaldTrump ahead in states Pres Obama won twice. https://t.co/EGySAz6Am1,True,2016-09-18T21:07:05,en,5587,13376,"[('medium', 1), ('poll', 1), ('showing', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('ahead', 1)]","[('Pres Obama', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/EGySAz6Am1', 'PERSON')]"
777494113834917888,realDonaldTrump,"I would like to express my warmest regards, best wishes and condolences to all of the families and victims of the horrible bombing in NYC.",False,2016-09-18T13:06:56,en,16269,53317,"[('would', 1), ('like', 1), ('express', 1), ('warmest', 1), ('regard', 1)]","[('NYC', 'LOC')]"
777284744253812740,realDonaldTrump,"Never met but never liked dopey Robert Gates. Look at the mess the U.S. is in. Always speaks badly of his many bosses, including Obama.",False,2016-09-17T23:14:58,en,5801,20616,"[('never', 2), ('met', 1), ('liked', 1), ('dopey', 1), ('robert', 1)]","[('Robert Gates', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Obama', 'PERSON')]"
777281927841587200,realDonaldTrump,"Heading to Colorado for a big rally. Massive crowd, great people! Will be there soon - the polls are looking good.",False,2016-09-17T23:03:47,en,5740,23202,"[('heading', 1), ('colorado', 1), ('big', 1), ('rally', 1), ('massive', 1)]","[('Colorado', 'GPE')]"
777280259875975169,realDonaldTrump,"My lawyers want to sue the failing @nytimes so badly for irresponsible intent. I said no (for now), but they are watching. Really disgusting",False,2016-09-17T22:57:09,en,7997,27792,"[('lawyer', 1), ('want', 1), ('sue', 1), ('failing', 1), ('nytimes', 1)]",[]
777260548991819776,realDonaldTrump,"The failing @nytimes has gone nuts that Crooked Hillary is doing so badly. They are willing to say anything, has become a laughingstock rag!",False,2016-09-17T21:38:50,en,10124,31796,"[('failing', 1), ('nytimes', 1), ('gone', 1), ('nut', 1), ('crooked', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777197786039103488,realDonaldTrump,"Crazy Maureen Dowd, the wacky columnist for the failing @nytimes, pretends she knows me well--wrong!",False,2016-09-17T17:29:26,en,5504,18734,"[('crazy', 1), ('maureen', 1), ('dowd', 1), ('wacky', 1), ('columnist', 1)]","[('Maureen Dowd', 'PERSON')]"
777197604887113728,realDonaldTrump,"Wacky @NYTimesDowd, who hardly knows me, makes up things that I never said for her boring interviews and column. A neurotic dope!",False,2016-09-17T17:28:43,en,6164,20873,"[('wacky', 1), ('nytimesdowd', 1), ('hardly', 1), ('know', 1), ('make', 1)]",[]
777133433915002880,realDonaldTrump,".@CNN just doesn't get it, and that's why their ratings are so low - and getting worse. Boring anti-Trump panelists, mostly losers in life!",False,2016-09-17T13:13:43,en,13052,40399,"[('cnn', 1), ('get', 1), ('rating', 1), ('low', 1), ('getting', 1)]","[('anti-Trump', 'PERSON')]"
777112789672341504,realDonaldTrump,I never met former Defense Secretary Robert Gates. He knows nothing about me. But look at the results under his guidance - a total disaster!,False,2016-09-17T11:51:41,en,7438,24418,"[('never', 1), ('met', 1), ('former', 1), ('defense', 1), ('secretary', 1)]","[('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Robert Gates', 'PERSON')]"
777022559367770112,realDonaldTrump,Crooked Hillary wants to take your 2nd Amendment rights away. Will guns be taken from her heavily armed Secret Service detail? Maybe not!,False,2016-09-17T05:53:09,en,14572,40447,"[('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('want', 1), ('take', 1), ('nd', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777015676586172417,realDonaldTrump,My thoughts and prayers go out to the @PhillyPolice &amp; @Penn police officers- in Philadelphia. https://t.co/eyC3W1mweY,False,2016-09-17T05:25:48,en,8438,21325,"[('thought', 1), ('prayer', 1), ('go', 1), ('phillypolice', 1), ('amp', 1)]","[('@PhillyPolice &', 'ORG'), ('Philadelphia', 'GPE')]"
777013142526185473,realDonaldTrump,"""Donald Trump’s birther event is the greatest trick he’s ever pulled""
https://t.co/zvVQnxeiQ9",False,2016-09-17T05:15:44,en,7094,19821,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('birther', 1), ('event', 1), ('greatest', 1)]","[('Donald Trump’s', 'PERSON')]"
777004964409335808,realDonaldTrump,A very interesting take from @KatiePavlich: https://t.co/XaM9yEYCHL,False,2016-09-17T04:43:14,en,5221,14480,"[('interesting', 1), ('take', 1), ('katiepavlich', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]",[]
776998082936315904,realDonaldTrump,Just arrived in Texas - have been informed two @fortworthpd officers have been shot. My thoughts and prayers are with them.,False,2016-09-17T04:15:53,en,8562,27178,"[('arrived', 1), ('texas', 1), ('informed', 1), ('two', 1), ('fortworthpd', 1)]","[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
776952133358751744,realDonaldTrump,"Just leaving Miami for Houston, Oklahoma and Colorado. Miami crowd was fantastic!",False,2016-09-17T01:13:18,en,5775,22866,"[('miami', 2), ('leaving', 1), ('houston', 1), ('oklahoma', 1), ('colorado', 1)]","[('Miami', 'GPE'), ('Houston', 'GPE'), ('Oklahoma', 'GPE'), ('Colorado', 'GPE'), ('Miami', 'GPE')]"
776888753499561984,realDonaldTrump,Great parade in The Villages- I love you all. We will #MAGA. Thank you for the incredible support-I will not forget! https://t.co/5qTDijU3hn,False,2016-09-16T21:01:27,en,10125,29487,"[('great', 1), ('parade', 1), ('village', 1), ('love', 1), ('maga', 1)]","[('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
776842647294009344,realDonaldTrump,I am truly honored and grateful for receiving SO much support from our American heroes...https://t.co/S9bvbysiOr https://t.co/JJQncd3zhf,False,2016-09-16T17:58:14,en,10380,27029,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('truly', 1), ('honored', 1), ('grateful', 1)]","[('American', 'NORP')]"
776773380414537728,realDonaldTrump,"I am now going to the brand new Trump International, Hotel D.C. for a major statement.",False,2016-09-16T13:23:00,en,6629,26806,"[('going', 1), ('brand', 1), ('new', 1), ('trump', 1), ('international', 1)]","[('Trump International', 'ORG')]"
776624517087133696,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you for a great evening - Laconia, New Hampshire -- will be back soon! #AmericaFirst
https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW https://t.co/QWbYm2lY7B",False,2016-09-16T03:31:28,en,5825,18426,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('great', 1), ('evening', 1)]","[('New Hampshire', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
776612349079855104,realDonaldTrump,"""@AK_TWEET: #TheDonald's hair gets the #JimmyFallon treatment on #TheTonightShow #TrumpPence16 https://t.co/0RRPbfIgXH""  So true!",False,2016-09-16T02:43:07,en,4411,15449,"[('ak', 1), ('tweet', 1), ('thedonald', 1), ('hair', 1), ('get', 1)]","[('TheDonald', 'ORG'), ('JimmyFallon', 'PRODUCT'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
776611024996823040,realDonaldTrump,"""@jimmyfallon: Tonight: @realDonaldTrump, @normmacdonald, a performance by Kiiara,and your funniest #MyTeacherIsWeird tweets. #FallonTonight",False,2016-09-16T02:37:51,en,2515,10484,"[('jimmyfallon', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('normmacdonald', 1), ('performance', 1)]","[('Tonight', 'TIME'), ('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('Kiiara', 'GPE'), ('FallonTonight', 'PRODUCT')]"
776552722195705857,realDonaldTrump,"Instead of driving jobs and wealth away, AMERICA will become the WORLD'S great magnet for innovation &amp; job creation! https://t.co/cvu20ZQSVJ",False,2016-09-15T22:46:11,en,10620,28813,"[('job', 2), ('instead', 1), ('driving', 1), ('wealth', 1), ('away', 1)]","[('AMERICA', 'GPE')]"
776551473475887104,realDonaldTrump,Will be joining @jimmyfallon on @FallonTonight at 11:35pmE tonight. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-15T22:41:13,en,3982,14369,"[('joining', 1), ('jimmyfallon', 1), ('fallontonight', 1), ('pme', 1), ('tonight', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
776547091816517632,realDonaldTrump,What a scary statistic! Americans are working harder and making less! We need competent leadership! https://t.co/jcGCbVOf6v,True,2016-09-15T22:23:48,en,10182,20471,"[('scary', 1), ('statistic', 1), ('american', 1), ('working', 1), ('harder', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
776528966668652544,realDonaldTrump,I will be interviewed by @jessebwatters on @oreillyfactor tonight at 8pm. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-15T21:11:47,en,3670,13724,"[('interviewed', 1), ('jessebwatters', 1), ('oreillyfactor', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('pm', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('8pm', 'TIME')]"
776468635955130368,realDonaldTrump,Full transcript of economic plan- delivered to the Economic Club of New York. #MAGA https://t.co/xiu9AUiSSD https://t.co/Fsy1diPWjU,False,2016-09-15T17:12:03,en,6015,16035,"[('economic', 2), ('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('full', 1), ('transcript', 1)]","[('the Economic Club of New York', 'ORG'), ('MAGA https://t.co/xiu9AUiSSD', 'PERSON')]"
776445262420123648,realDonaldTrump,Thank you @JerryJrFalwell! https://t.co/jzUQxkW4tB,False,2016-09-15T15:39:10,en,3381,11030,"[('thank', 1), ('jerryjrfalwell', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('jzuqxkw', 1)]",[]
776432922450616320,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you to all of our law enforcement officers - across America! #LESM #MAGA 
https://t.co/Mcbc2JzhN2 https://t.co/4MTmR8kXVb",False,2016-09-15T14:50:08,en,8662,23766,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('law', 1), ('enforcement', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/Mcbc2JzhN2 https://t.co/4MTmR8kXVb', 'PERSON')]"
776428916303138816,realDonaldTrump,Thank you for having me! I enjoyed the tour and spending time with everyone. See you soon. #MAGA https://t.co/eNtS7IBPDo,False,2016-09-15T14:34:13,en,3694,13080,"[('thank', 1), ('enjoyed', 1), ('tour', 1), ('spending', 1), ('time', 1)]","[('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
776372090068955136,realDonaldTrump,Will be on @foxandfriends at 7:00 A.M. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-15T10:48:25,en,2118,10978,"[('foxandfriends', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('7:00 A.M. Enjoy', 'DATE')]"
776270376846422017,realDonaldTrump,"""@ghfanlovessonny: @realDonaldTrump you have my vote in Pennsylvania. Trump 2016"" Thank you!",False,2016-09-15T04:04:14,en,3481,14173,"[('ghfanlovessonny', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('vote', 1), ('pennsylvania', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('Pennsylvania', 'GPE'), ('2016', 'DATE')]"
776269061823074304,realDonaldTrump,I was never a fan of Colin Powell after his weak understanding of weapons of mass destruction in Iraq = disaster. We can do much better!,False,2016-09-15T03:59:01,en,7876,27608,"[('never', 1), ('fan', 1), ('colin', 1), ('powell', 1), ('weak', 1)]","[('Colin Powell', 'PERSON'), ('Iraq', 'GPE')]"
776254365627719680,realDonaldTrump,I will be interviewed on @foxandfriends tomorrow at 7am. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-15T03:00:37,en,3031,12641,"[('interviewed', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1), ('tomorrow', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('7am', 'TIME')]"
776247579600453632,realDonaldTrump,"Great poll out of Nevada- thank you! See you soon. #MAGA #AmericaFirst
https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW https://t.co/27sR3MjjXc",False,2016-09-15T02:33:39,en,6649,20014,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('great', 1), ('poll', 1), ('nevada', 1)]","[('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW', 'PERSON')]"
776223340595937280,realDonaldTrump,"Great evening in Canton, Ohio-thank you! We are going to MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN! Join us: 
https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW https://t.co/4MvwUj9eX9",False,2016-09-15T00:57:20,en,6225,19219,"[('great', 2), ('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('evening', 1), ('canton', 1)]","[('evening', 'TIME'), ('Canton', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!', 'EVENT')]"
776213027989426176,realDonaldTrump,Honor to have been interviewed by the very wonderful @bishopwtjackson in Detroit last week - tune in at 9pmE. Enjoy! https://t.co/9ahPnfhQ5N,False,2016-09-15T00:16:21,en,3930,13204,"[('honor', 1), ('interviewed', 1), ('wonderful', 1), ('bishopwtjackson', 1), ('detroit', 1)]","[('Detroit', 'GPE'), ('last week', 'DATE')]"
776169656080039936,realDonaldTrump,Thank you Ohio! Just landed in Canton for a rally at the Civic Center. Join me at 7pm: https://t.co/s0XVVNyBKf https://t.co/UtCRxykurW,False,2016-09-14T21:24:01,en,8148,24359,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('landed', 1)]","[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Canton', 'GPE'), ('the Civic Center', 'FAC')]"
776160185337413632,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Florida- can't wait to see you Friday in Miami! Join me:
https://t.co/rsx313493u https://t.co/JxsWXz05T9",False,2016-09-14T20:46:23,en,7294,20281,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('florida', 1), ('wait', 1)]","[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Miami', 'GPE')]"
776101877805158400,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you @ATFD17! #ImWithYou
Video: https://t.co/z9Yg83VTF4",False,2016-09-14T16:54:41,en,2718,9420,"[('thank', 1), ('atfd', 1), ('imwithyou', 1), ('video', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
776058538137452548,realDonaldTrump,"Great poll Florida - thank you! 
#ImWithYou #AmericaFirst https://t.co/6Odle7j1hd",False,2016-09-14T14:02:28,en,11665,34069,"[('great', 1), ('poll', 1), ('florida', 1), ('thank', 1), ('imwithyou', 1)]","[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
776053900780695553,realDonaldTrump,Thank you Ohio - see you tonight! https://t.co/0DyHkzzWvj,False,2016-09-14T13:44:02,en,7730,23192,"[('thank', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('see', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('https://t.co/0DyHkzzWvj', 'GPE')]"
775897251533160448,realDonaldTrump,Russia took Crimea during the so-called Obama years. Who wouldn't know this and why does Obama get a free pass?,False,2016-09-14T03:21:34,en,8090,23011,"[('obama', 2), ('russia', 1), ('took', 1), ('crimea', 1), ('called', 1)]","[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Crimea', 'PERSON'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
775894243143483392,realDonaldTrump,Why isn't President Obama working instead of campaigning for Hillary Clinton?,False,2016-09-14T03:09:37,en,24978,62783,"[('president', 1), ('obama', 1), ('working', 1), ('instead', 1), ('campaigning', 1)]","[('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
775888611615080448,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Rep. @CynthiaLummis!
https://t.co/4S4pnx4Q6r https://t.co/PLUKlsPXPR",False,2016-09-14T02:47:14,en,4148,12228,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('rep', 1), ('cynthialummis', 1)]","[('@CynthiaLummis', 'PERSON')]"
775888025213599744,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Rep. @MarshaBlackburn!
https://t.co/vxEk0X4ntS https://t.co/9gAk0FWqZ8",False,2016-09-14T02:44:55,en,4059,11959,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('rep', 1), ('marshablackburn', 1)]","[('@MarshaBlackburn', 'PERSON')]"
775887550506536960,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you @RepReneeEllmers!
https://t.co/1DrZpfa6je https://t.co/rzEw8pQhds",False,2016-09-14T02:43:01,en,3758,11225,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('repreneeellmers', 1), ('drzpfa', 1)]",[]
775886838502481921,realDonaldTrump,Trump outlines new child-care policy proposals via the @FoxNews App @realDonaldTrump seems a candidate of destiny https://t.co/ZktSYF01SH,True,2016-09-14T02:40:12,en,3830,9659,"[('trump', 1), ('outline', 1), ('new', 1), ('child', 1), ('care', 1)]",[]
775883010508029953,realDonaldTrump,"CHILD CARE REFORMS THAT WILL MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
Transcript: https://t.co/rntyxBSb9J
https://t.co/5SWmxfVfto https://t.co/j389Quo4bg",False,2016-09-14T02:24:59,en,7172,18611,"[('http', 3), ('co', 3), ('j', 2), ('child', 1), ('care', 1)]","[('CHILD CARE REFORMS THAT', 'PERSON'), ('Transcript', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/5SWmxfVfto', 'PERSON')]"
775826926560608256,realDonaldTrump,"Ivanka penned an Op-Ed that ran in the @WSJ this afternoon, read it here. https://t.co/3QE4nRXzLZ @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/OFyemRve4j",True,2016-09-13T22:42:08,en,4080,11587,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('ivanka', 1), ('penned', 1), ('op', 1)]","[('this afternoon', 'TIME')]"
775787262869180417,realDonaldTrump,Ivanka is joining @realDonaldTrump to outline an innovative new child care policy to support American families. Tune in to watch live at 7pm,True,2016-09-13T20:04:31,en,4231,13494,"[('ivanka', 1), ('joining', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('outline', 1), ('innovative', 1)]","[('American', 'NORP'), ('7pm', 'TIME')]"
775781315081740289,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Clive, Iowa!
https://t.co/tuZ35BkD9J",False,2016-09-13T19:40:53,en,2893,11579,"[('thank', 1), ('clive', 1), ('iowa', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('Iowa', 'GPE')]"
775710725926952961,realDonaldTrump,"Join us today! Together, we will 
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain!
https://t.co/v40n8RXgti https://t.co/e3KQfBR2K8",False,2016-09-13T15:00:23,en,5259,15825,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('u', 1), ('today', 1)]",[]
775683959061708800,realDonaldTrump,"Heading to Iowa- join me today at noon! #MakeAmericaGreatAgain
Tickets: https://t.co/TEY6BbCyxt https://t.co/QyR2MDYYbZ",False,2016-09-13T13:14:02,en,4182,14663,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('heading', 1), ('iowa', 1), ('join', 1)]","[('today', 'DATE'), ('noon', 'TIME')]"
775534440240013312,realDonaldTrump,"Join me in Clive, Iowa tomorrow at noon! #AmericaFirst #MAGA
Tickets: https://t.co/TEY6BbCyxt https://t.co/l17uzRPyLs",False,2016-09-13T03:19:53,en,4209,13850,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('clive', 1), ('iowa', 1)]","[('Clive', 'GPE'), ('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('noon', 'TIME'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
775496470816514048,realDonaldTrump,"""@brimyers813: Saw ur speech on Twitter. U give me hope and optimism. I feel as though I am in the room with u. I pray 4 ur/our success.""",False,2016-09-13T00:49:01,en,5247,19747,"[('ur', 2), ('u', 2), ('brimyers', 1), ('saw', 1), ('speech', 1)]","[('Twitter', 'PRODUCT'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
775492989175160836,realDonaldTrump,"Just got back from Asheville,  North Carolina, where we had a massive rally. The spirit of the crowd was unbelievable. Thank you!  #MAGA",False,2016-09-13T00:35:11,en,8089,31963,"[('got', 1), ('back', 1), ('asheville', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1)]","[('Asheville', 'GPE'), ('North Carolina', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
775361266001084416,realDonaldTrump,Stopped by @TrumpDC to thank all of the tremendous men &amp; women for their hard work! https://t.co/oGcJL4N454,False,2016-09-12T15:51:45,en,9307,31790,"[('stopped', 1), ('trumpdc', 1), ('thank', 1), ('tremendous', 1), ('men', 1)]","[('@TrumpDC', 'ORG')]"
775293160838819841,realDonaldTrump,Will be on @CNBC at @7:22. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-12T11:21:08,en,2364,11736,"[('cnbc', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('@CNBC', 'ORG'), ('@7:22', 'ORG')]"
775275158340853760,realDonaldTrump,I will be interviewed on @foxandfriends at 7:00 A.M.,False,2016-09-12T10:09:36,en,3146,15094,"[('interviewed', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1)]","[('7:00 A.M.', 'TIME')]"
774778026479513600,realDonaldTrump,"The seriously failing @nytimes, despite so much winning and poll numbers that will soon put me in first place, only writes dishonest hits!",False,2016-09-11T01:14:10,en,8029,28617,"[('seriously', 1), ('failing', 1), ('nytimes', 1), ('despite', 1), ('much', 1)]","[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
774753598970466304,realDonaldTrump,Hillary Clinton just had her 47% moment. What a terrible thing she said about so many great Americans!,False,2016-09-10T23:37:06,en,15750,45862,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('moment', 1), ('terrible', 1), ('thing', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('47%', 'PERCENT'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
774710663373520897,realDonaldTrump,"RT if you agree: We need a President who is fighting for all Americans, not one who writes off nearly half the country.",True,2016-09-10T20:46:30,en,27727,29489,"[('rt', 1), ('agree', 1), ('need', 1), ('president', 1), ('fighting', 1)]","[('RT', 'ORG'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('nearly half', 'CARDINAL')]"
774673449885192192,realDonaldTrump,"While Hillary said horrible things about my supporters, and while many of her supporters will never vote for me, I still respect them all!",False,2016-09-10T18:18:37,en,25877,71698,"[('supporter', 2), ('hillary', 1), ('said', 1), ('horrible', 1), ('thing', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
774637168769830912,realDonaldTrump,"Really sad that Republicans would allow themselves to be used in a Clinton ad. Lindsey Graham, Romney, Flake, Sass. SUPREME COURT, REMEMBER!",False,2016-09-10T15:54:27,en,12132,36449,"[('really', 1), ('sad', 1), ('republican', 1), ('would', 1), ('allow', 1)]","[('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Romney, Flake', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Sass', 'ORG'), ('SUPREME COURT', 'ORG')]"
774590070355529728,realDonaldTrump,"Wow, Hillary Clinton was SO INSULTING to my supporters, millions of amazing, hard working people. I think it will cost her at the Polls!",False,2016-09-10T12:47:18,en,21987,62361,"[('wow', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('insulting', 1), ('supporter', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
774589019929866240,realDonaldTrump,"Will be in Missouri today with Melania for the funeral of a wonderful and truly respected woman, Phyllis S!",False,2016-09-10T12:43:08,en,6057,24673,"[('missouri', 1), ('today', 1), ('melania', 1), ('funeral', 1), ('wonderful', 1)]","[('Missouri', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Melania', 'GPE'), ('Phyllis S', 'PERSON')]"
774585883165093888,realDonaldTrump,"""@Stvzbnk: Just Watched @tonyschwartz. Obviously Tony is a Total Whack Job @realDonaldTrump""",False,2016-09-10T12:30:40,en,2447,10498,"[('stvzbnk', 1), ('watched', 1), ('tonyschwartz', 1), ('obviously', 1), ('tony', 1)]","[('Tony', 'PERSON')]"
774491376906100736,realDonaldTrump,"Just returned from Pensacola, Florida, where the crowd was incredible.",False,2016-09-10T06:15:08,en,4782,21270,"[('returned', 1), ('pensacola', 1), ('florida', 1), ('crowd', 1), ('incredible', 1)]","[('Pensacola', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
774487060384276480,realDonaldTrump,"I havn't seen @tonyschwartz in many years, he hardly knows me. Never liked his style. Super lib, Crooked H supporter. Irrelevant dope!",False,2016-09-10T05:57:59,en,4370,17421,"[('havn', 1), ('seen', 1), ('tonyschwartz', 1), ('many', 1), ('year', 1)]","[('many years', 'DATE')]"
774484342030602240,realDonaldTrump,"Dummy writer @tonyschwartz, who wanted to do a second book with me for years (I said no), is now a hostile basket case who feels jilted!",False,2016-09-10T05:47:11,en,4430,16879,"[('dummy', 1), ('writer', 1), ('tonyschwartz', 1), ('wanted', 1), ('second', 1)]","[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
774435151975747584,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Florida - we are going to MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN! Join us: https://t.co/3KWOl2ibaW. 
#AmericaFirst https://t.co/vzKtRxzvwv",False,2016-09-10T02:31:43,en,7012,20318,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('florida', 1), ('going', 1)]","[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!', 'EVENT'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
774399833733947393,realDonaldTrump,"Will be delivering a major speech tonight - live on @oreillyfactor at 8:10pm from Pensacola, Florida.",False,2016-09-10T00:11:22,en,3591,14762,"[('delivering', 1), ('major', 1), ('speech', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('live', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('8:10pm', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pensacola', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
774386793038778368,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Ohio. Together, we will MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
https://t.co/3KWOl20zMm https://t.co/n026nE4XIp",False,2016-09-09T23:19:33,en,8581,23027,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('together', 1)]","[('Ohio', 'GPE')]"
774385288948817920,realDonaldTrump,Great honor to be endorsed by popular &amp; successful @gov_gilmore of VA. A state that I very much want to win-THX Jim! https://t.co/x4Y1TAFHvn,False,2016-09-09T23:13:34,en,7791,22035,"[('great', 1), ('honor', 1), ('endorsed', 1), ('popular', 1), ('amp', 1)]","[('@gov_gilmore of VA', 'FAC')]"
774354404162039808,realDonaldTrump,"MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!
#AmericaFirst #ImWithYou https://t.co/JIlNW7myEN",False,2016-09-09T21:10:51,en,9976,21857,"[('make', 1), ('america', 1), ('great', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('imwithyou', 1)]",[]
774299479155544064,realDonaldTrump,"Henry McMaster, Lt. Governor of South Carolina who endorsed me, beat failed @CNN announcer Bakari Sellers, so badly. Funny!",False,2016-09-09T17:32:36,en,5184,17485,"[('henry', 1), ('mcmaster', 1), ('lt', 1), ('governor', 1), ('south', 1)]","[('Henry McMaster', 'PERSON'), ('South Carolina', 'GPE'), ('@CNN', 'ORG'), ('Bakari Sellers', 'PERSON')]"
774281441144344576,realDonaldTrump,Join @TeamTrump on Saturday for National Day of Action as we work to #MakeAmericaGreatAgain! https://t.co/hyclkzPoBR https://t.co/0DWIvJpoJG,True,2016-09-09T16:20:55,en,4134,11181,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('teamtrump', 1), ('saturday', 1)]","[('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('National Day of Action', 'EVENT')]"
774256782290128896,realDonaldTrump,Jeff Zucker failed @NBC and he is now failing @CNN.,False,2016-09-09T14:42:56,en,4535,14841,"[('jeff', 1), ('zucker', 1), ('failed', 1), ('nbc', 1), ('failing', 1)]","[('Jeff Zucker', 'PERSON'), ('@CNN', 'ORG')]"
774255510191239170,realDonaldTrump,".@CNN is unwatchable. Their news on me is fiction. They
are a disgrace to the broadcasting industry and an arm of the Clinton campaign.",False,2016-09-09T14:37:53,en,15768,43883,"[('cnn', 1), ('unwatchable', 1), ('news', 1), ('fiction', 1), ('disgrace', 1)]","[('Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
774097705513517057,realDonaldTrump,The documentary of me that @CNN just aired is a total waste of time. I don't even know many of the people who spoke about me. A joke!,False,2016-09-09T04:10:49,en,8269,27108,"[('documentary', 1), ('cnn', 1), ('aired', 1), ('total', 1), ('waste', 1)]",[]
774064919633428480,realDonaldTrump,Final poll results from NBC on last nights Commander-in-Chief Forum. Thank you! #ImWithYou #MAGA https://t.co/C5ipaxUN7B,False,2016-09-09T02:00:32,en,10735,27943,"[('final', 1), ('poll', 1), ('result', 1), ('nbc', 1), ('last', 1)]","[('NBC', 'ORG'), ('last nights', 'DATE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
774044548293074944,realDonaldTrump,It wasn't Matt Lauer that hurt Hillary last night. It was her very dumb answer about emails &amp; the veteran who said she should be in jail.,False,2016-09-09T00:39:36,en,15285,44543,"[('matt', 1), ('lauer', 1), ('hurt', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('last', 1)]","[('Matt Lauer', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
774033670239760384,realDonaldTrump,"More poll results from last nights Commander-in-Chief Forum. 
#AmericaFirst #TrumpTrain https://t.co/FxyBL6fO1h",False,2016-09-08T23:56:22,en,10513,26036,"[('poll', 1), ('result', 1), ('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('commander', 1)]","[('last nights', 'DATE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
773972305642913792,realDonaldTrump,Last nights results - in poll taken by NBC. #AmericaFirst #ImWithYou https://t.co/sCOnny1fl3,False,2016-09-08T19:52:32,en,15838,38028,"[('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('result', 1), ('poll', 1), ('taken', 1)]","[('Last nights', 'DATE'), ('NBC', 'ORG'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
773948271140016128,realDonaldTrump,"With Luis, Mexico and the United States would have made wonderful deals together - where both Mexico and the US would have benefitted.",False,2016-09-08T18:17:01,en,5009,17285,"[('mexico', 2), ('would', 2), ('luis', 1), ('united', 1), ('state', 1)]","[('Luis', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
773948120069615616,realDonaldTrump,Mexico has lost a brilliant finance minister and wonderful man who I know is highly respected by President Peña Nieto.,False,2016-09-08T18:16:25,en,4896,17623,"[('mexico', 1), ('lost', 1), ('brilliant', 1), ('finance', 1), ('minister', 1)]","[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Peña Nieto', 'PERSON')]"
773920230192054272,realDonaldTrump,Hillary Clinton answered email questions differently last night than she has in the past. She is totally confused. Unfit to serve as #POTUS.,False,2016-09-08T16:25:36,en,10678,31255,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('answered', 1), ('email', 1), ('question', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('last night', 'TIME')]"
773903163296473088,realDonaldTrump,Hillary just gave a disastrous news conference on the tarmac to make up for poor performance last night. She's being decimated by the media!,False,2016-09-08T15:17:47,en,11264,35998,"[('hillary', 1), ('gave', 1), ('disastrous', 1), ('news', 1), ('conference', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('last night', 'TIME')]"
773901007340310528,realDonaldTrump,Last nights winner was clear &amp; it will be proven time &amp; time again - lets #MAGA!! Lets WIN!! #TrumpTrain https://t.co/sGqp9rGmBH,True,2016-09-08T15:09:13,en,7178,17673,"[('amp', 2), ('time', 2), ('let', 2), ('last', 1), ('night', 1)]","[('Last nights', 'DATE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('TrumpTrain', 'MONEY')]"
773855962528620548,realDonaldTrump,"""A rough night for Hillary Clinton""  ABC News.",False,2016-09-08T12:10:13,en,8941,29965,"[('rough', 1), ('night', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('abc', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('ABC News', 'ORG')]"
773836389943246848,realDonaldTrump,"Wow, reviews are in - THANK YOU!",False,2016-09-08T10:52:27,en,5212,22331,"[('wow', 1), ('review', 1), ('thank', 1)]",[]
773834064465920000,realDonaldTrump,COMING UP @GenFlynn @newtgingrich on @foxandfriends,False,2016-09-08T10:43:12,en,2326,10877,"[('coming', 1), ('genflynn', 1), ('newtgingrich', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1)]",[]
773833021837438977,realDonaldTrump,Thank you to @foxandfriends for the nice reviews of last night.,False,2016-09-08T10:39:04,en,3929,16814,"[('thank', 1), ('foxandfriends', 1), ('nice', 1), ('review', 1), ('last', 1)]","[('last night', 'TIME')]"
773823089331277824,realDonaldTrump,Thank you America - great #CommanderInChiefForum polls! https://t.co/Rcu6KaRGCB,False,2016-09-08T09:59:36,en,9687,23543,"[('thank', 1), ('america', 1), ('great', 1), ('commanderinchiefforum', 1), ('poll', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('https://t.co/Rcu6KaRGCB', 'GPE')]"
773733162245582849,realDonaldTrump,Thank you to our fantastic veterans. The reviews and polls from almost everyone of my Commander-in-Chief presentation were great. Nice!,False,2016-09-08T04:02:15,en,9500,37224,"[('thank', 1), ('fantastic', 1), ('veteran', 1), ('review', 1), ('poll', 1)]",[]
773643843476611072,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Peter - if elected, I will think big for our country &amp; never let the American people down! #AmericaFirst https://t.co/6Nwu7EMJ9d",False,2016-09-07T22:07:20,en,8382,22041,"[('thank', 1), ('peter', 1), ('elected', 1), ('think', 1), ('big', 1)]","[('Peter - if', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
773617820944961536,realDonaldTrump,"Wow - thank you Pensacola, FL. See you Friday at 7pm -- join me!
https://t.co/JCO7Za78tV https://t.co/LYmpRyY0Hq",False,2016-09-07T20:23:56,en,7075,22533,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('wow', 1), ('thank', 1), ('pensacola', 1)]","[('Pensacola', 'PERSON'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('7pm', 'TIME'), ('https://t.co/LYmpRyY0Hq', 'PERSON')]"
773539317377478657,realDonaldTrump,"'Donald Trump leads Hillary Clinton by 19 points among military, veteran voters: poll' #AmericaFirst #MAGA
https://t.co/5FmxGtLkwt",False,2016-09-07T15:11:59,en,8618,22958,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('lead', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/5FmxGtLkwt', 'PERSON')]"
773375897554526208,realDonaldTrump,"""@adhd_fa:Kudos to @PARISDENNARD for standing up to CNN's attempt to bully you and shout you down for defending @realDonaldTrump #media bias",False,2016-09-07T04:22:37,en,5298,17312,"[('adhd', 1), ('fa', 1), ('kudos', 1), ('parisdennard', 1), ('standing', 1)]","[('@PARISDENNARD', 'ORG'), ('CNN', 'ORG'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
773330142785630208,realDonaldTrump,I will be interviewed on @oreillyfactor tonight at 11pmE @FoxNews. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-07T01:20:48,en,3096,13398,"[('interviewed', 1), ('oreillyfactor', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('pme', 1), ('foxnews', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('11pmE @FoxNews', 'DATE')]"
773318106630463488,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you North Carolina- get out &amp; #VoteTrump on 11/8/2016!
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain https://t.co/HX2LRYs4Vq",False,2016-09-07T00:32:58,en,6536,19531,"[('thank', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1), ('get', 1), ('amp', 1)]","[('North', 'PERSON'), ('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('VoteTrump', 'PRODUCT'), ('11/8/2016', 'CARDINAL'), ('#MakeAmericaGreatAgain', 'PERSON')]"
773281879848062976,realDonaldTrump,"Great meeting with military spouses in Virginia- joined by @IvankaTrump, @LaraLeaTrump, @GenFlynn &amp; @MayorRGiuliani. https://t.co/00GNH9nLet",False,2016-09-06T22:09:01,en,6407,19108,"[('great', 1), ('meeting', 1), ('military', 1), ('spouse', 1), ('virginia', 1)]",[]
773250022045548544,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you to all of our amazing military families, service members, and veterans. #ImWithYou https://t.co/RmQJt0Wxcq",False,2016-09-06T20:02:26,en,8472,26346,"[('thank', 1), ('amazing', 1), ('military', 1), ('family', 1), ('service', 1)]","[('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
773218706084290565,realDonaldTrump,"Join me in Pensacola, Florida this Friday at 7pm! #VoteTrump 
https://t.co/L8Ui56dcrJ https://t.co/0ciDCuoFeO",False,2016-09-06T17:57:59,en,4819,14298,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('pensacola', 1), ('florida', 1)]","[('Pensacola', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('this Friday', 'DATE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('#VoteTrump \r\n', 'MONEY')]"
773206341296979972,realDonaldTrump,Thank you! #VoteTrump #ImWithYou https://t.co/SCEq9LqTTj,False,2016-09-06T17:08:51,en,12785,33970,"[('thank', 1), ('votetrump', 1), ('imwithyou', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]",[]
773181751749402624,realDonaldTrump,"Mainstream media never covered Hillary’s massive “hacking”
or coughing attack, yet it is #1 trending. What’s up?",False,2016-09-06T15:31:09,en,14388,36990,"[('mainstream', 1), ('medium', 1), ('never', 1), ('covered', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'MONEY')]"
773145023319867392,realDonaldTrump,"""@Ler: Message for undecided voters: Please wake up and vote DonaldTrump now! Trump/Pence very important save our America before too late!""",False,2016-09-06T13:05:12,en,6723,20412,"[('ler', 1), ('message', 1), ('undecided', 1), ('voter', 1), ('please', 1)]","[('@Ler: Message', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('DonaldTrump', 'ORG'), ('Trump/Pence', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
773140953133641729,realDonaldTrump,Thank you! #AmericaFirst https://t.co/6v4C8ykDVl,False,2016-09-06T12:49:02,en,10859,28653,"[('thank', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('v', 1)]","[('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
773140702972801024,realDonaldTrump,"As a tribute to the late, great Phyllis Schlafly, I hope everybody can go out and get her latest book, THE CONSERVATIVE CASE FOR TRUMP.",False,2016-09-06T12:48:02,en,5727,18968,"[('tribute', 1), ('late', 1), ('great', 1), ('phyllis', 1), ('schlafly', 1)]","[('Phyllis Schlafly', 'PERSON')]"
773116580733587456,realDonaldTrump,"China wouldn't provide a red carpet stairway from Air Force One and then Philippines President calls Obama ""the son of a whore."" Terrible!",False,2016-09-06T11:12:11,en,11104,31681,"[('china', 1), ('provide', 1), ('red', 1), ('carpet', 1), ('stairway', 1)]","[('China', 'GPE'), ('Air Force One', 'PRODUCT'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('Obama', 'PERSON')]"
773113752271060992,realDonaldTrump,"The truly great Phyllis Schlafly, who honored me with her strong endorsement for president, has passed away at 92. She was very special!",False,2016-09-06T11:00:56,en,7113,26935,"[('truly', 1), ('great', 1), ('phyllis', 1), ('schlafly', 1), ('honored', 1)]","[('Phyllis Schlafly', 'PERSON'), ('92', 'DATE')]"
772928797419143168,realDonaldTrump,Thank you Ohio! #AmericaFirst https://t.co/p68GAJdhwu,False,2016-09-05T22:46:00,en,9539,26563,"[('thank', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
772863407620034560,realDonaldTrump,"Heading to Youngstown, Ohio now- some great polls. #AmericaFirst https://t.co/cGwDLSOFUt",False,2016-09-05T18:26:10,en,10440,26448,"[('heading', 1), ('youngstown', 1), ('ohio', 1), ('great', 1), ('poll', 1)]","[('Youngstown', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
772840545668493312,realDonaldTrump,Thank you American Legion Post 610- for hosting @Mike_Pence &amp; I for a roundtable with labor leaders. #LaborDay #MAGA https://t.co/r0cwJlV38L,False,2016-09-05T16:55:19,en,5986,19280,"[('thank', 1), ('american', 1), ('legion', 1), ('post', 1), ('hosting', 1)]","[('American Legion Post', 'ORG'), ('#LaborDay #', 'MONEY'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
772798809508372480,realDonaldTrump,"#LaborDay #AmericaFirst
Video: https://t.co/RNl7cfzkmN https://t.co/ZqRtbV4KRI",False,2016-09-05T14:09:28,en,5977,16226,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('laborday', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('video', 1)]","[('#LaborDay #', 'MONEY'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
772797202922082304,realDonaldTrump,Can you believe that the Chinese would not give Obama the proper stairway to get off his plane - fight on tarmac! https://t.co/FAldS5zZi5,False,2016-09-05T14:03:05,en,7846,19333,"[('believe', 1), ('chinese', 1), ('would', 1), ('give', 1), ('obama', 1)]","[('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
772793658072559616,realDonaldTrump,President Obama &amp; Putin fail to reach deal on Syria - so what else is new? Obama is not a natural deal maker. Only makes bad deals!,False,2016-09-05T13:49:00,en,9669,29131,"[('deal', 3), ('obama', 2), ('president', 1), ('amp', 1), ('putin', 1)]","[('Obama &', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Obama', 'PERSON')]"
772645423097995264,realDonaldTrump,"""@OSPREY675: @Miami4Trump I followed you because you are a patriot &amp; support @realDonaldTrump, as do I. #MAGA by sticking together.",False,2016-09-05T03:59:58,en,3784,14209,"[('osprey', 1), ('miami', 1), ('trump', 1), ('followed', 1), ('patriot', 1)]","[('I. #', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
772645091802480640,realDonaldTrump,"""@tweak626: I'm at a biker rally in Perry, Kansas...and everyone is a @realDonaldTrump fan. Love it.""",False,2016-09-05T03:58:39,en,4813,17781,"[('tweak', 1), ('biker', 1), ('rally', 1), ('perry', 1), ('kansa', 1)]","[('Perry', 'GPE'), ('Kansas', 'GPE')]"
772607833275830272,realDonaldTrump,"""@ronnieclemmons: @ChrisCJackson @TakouiS @realDonaldTrump  Trump now leads her by 2 - get real, she will lose big""",False,2016-09-05T01:30:36,en,4483,15870,"[('ronnieclemmons', 1), ('chriscjackson', 1), ('takouis', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
772607185851408387,realDonaldTrump,"""@lblackvelvet: @realDonaldTrump We need to show Americans that Hillary will KILL our Country !! Vote for Trump !!""",False,2016-09-05T01:28:02,en,5810,18922,"[('lblackvelvet', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('need', 1), ('show', 1), ('american', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('KILL', 'ORG')]"
772606281576280064,realDonaldTrump,"""@CherNuna: @realDonaldTrump It defies belief the Web of Lies Hillary is spinning! One excuse after another. Then it's this, then it's that.",False,2016-09-05T01:24:26,en,4916,16330,"[('chernuna', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('defies', 1), ('belief', 1), ('web', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
772582467601588224,realDonaldTrump,"Lyin' Hillary Clinton told the FBI that she did not know the ""C"" markings on documents stood for CLASSIFIED. How can this be happening?",False,2016-09-04T23:49:48,en,19509,49578,"[('lyin', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('told', 1), ('fbi', 1)]","[('Lyin', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('FBI', 'ORG')]"
772576650718482432,realDonaldTrump,"To the African-American community: The Democrats have failed you for fifty years, high crime, poor schools, no jobs. I will fix it, VOTE ""T""",False,2016-09-04T23:26:41,en,12743,37448,"[('african', 1), ('american', 1), ('community', 1), ('democrat', 1), ('failed', 1)]","[('African-American', 'NORP'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('fifty years', 'DATE'), ('VOTE', 'ORG')]"
772574369633763329,realDonaldTrump,The polls are close so Crooked Hillary is getting out of bed and will campaign tomorrow.Why did she hammer 13 devices and acid-wash e-mails?,False,2016-09-04T23:17:38,en,14314,36356,"[('poll', 1), ('close', 1), ('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('getting', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('13', 'CARDINAL')]"
772571293438840832,realDonaldTrump,"The Great State of Arizona, where I just had a massive rally (amazing people), has a very weak and ineffective Senator, Jeff Flake. Sad!",False,2016-09-04T23:05:24,en,6188,21427,"[('great', 1), ('state', 1), ('arizona', 1), ('massive', 1), ('rally', 1)]","[('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('Jeff Flake', 'PERSON')]"
772556213313765377,realDonaldTrump,"The Republican Party needs strong and committed leaders, not weak people such as @JeffFlake, if it is going to stop illegal immigration.",False,2016-09-04T22:05:29,en,7233,22192,"[('republican', 1), ('party', 1), ('need', 1), ('strong', 1), ('committed', 1)]","[('The Republican Party', 'ORG')]"
772473194162905089,realDonaldTrump,Doesn't fit the MSM narrative - so they wont share what @realDonaldTrump did for Jesse Jackson in 1999 - so I will! https://t.co/qzbyxOsruU,True,2016-09-04T16:35:36,en,13146,18443,"[('fit', 1), ('msm', 1), ('narrative', 1), ('wont', 1), ('share', 1)]","[('MSM', 'ORG'), ('Jesse Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('1999', 'DATE')]"
772467120114397184,realDonaldTrump,"""@AnneBellar: @realDonaldTrump @CNN CNN is so biased. Never ever watch them. Trump 2016!!""",False,2016-09-04T16:11:27,en,5902,19156,"[('cnn', 2), ('annebellar', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('biased', 1), ('never', 1)]","[('CNN', 'ORG'), ('2016', 'DATE')]"
772465330740404225,realDonaldTrump,Crooked Hillary's V.P. pick said this morning that I was not aware that Russia took over Crimea. A total lie - and taken over during O term!,False,2016-09-04T16:04:21,en,6954,22297,"[('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('v', 1), ('p', 1), ('pick', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('V.P.', 'PERSON'), ('this morning', 'TIME'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
772417922279043073,realDonaldTrump,"Wow, the failing @nytimes has not reported properly on Crooked's FBI release. They are at the back of the pack - no longer a credible source",False,2016-09-04T12:55:58,en,9658,29942,"[('wow', 1), ('failing', 1), ('nytimes', 1), ('reported', 1), ('properly', 1)]","[('FBI', 'ORG')]"
772171469476552704,realDonaldTrump,".@CNN is so disgusting in their bias, but they are having a hard time promoting Crooked Hillary in light of the new e-mail scandals.",False,2016-09-03T20:36:39,en,14280,41139,"[('cnn', 1), ('disgusting', 1), ('bias', 1), ('hard', 1), ('time', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
772170704687099904,realDonaldTrump,"Great visit to Detroit church, fantastic reception, and all @CNN talks about is a small protest outside. Inside a large and wonderful crowd!",False,2016-09-03T20:33:36,en,12037,38118,"[('great', 1), ('visit', 1), ('detroit', 1), ('church', 1), ('fantastic', 1)]","[('Detroit', 'GPE')]"
772166085974130697,realDonaldTrump,"I am returning to the Pensacola Bay Center in Florida- Friday, 9/9/16 at 7pm. Join me! https://t.co/L8Ui56dcrJ https://t.co/wAePlfS0JL",False,2016-09-03T20:15:15,en,6380,18999,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('returning', 1), ('pensacola', 1), ('bay', 1)]","[('the Pensacola Bay Center', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('7pm', 'TIME')]"
772123965938597888,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Great Faith Ministries International, Bishop Wayne T. Jackson, and Detroit!
https://t.co/4Ucx678ZCC",False,2016-09-03T17:27:53,en,11097,28965,"[('thank', 1), ('great', 1), ('faith', 1), ('ministry', 1), ('international', 1)]","[('Great Faith Ministries International', 'ORG'), ('Wayne T. Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Detroit', 'GPE'), ('https://t.co/4Ucx678ZCC', 'PERSON')]"
771753541698523136,realDonaldTrump,"Great new poll Iowa - thank you!
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain #ImWithYou https://t.co/7hupah1RQN",False,2016-09-02T16:55:57,en,10351,25711,"[('great', 1), ('new', 1), ('poll', 1), ('iowa', 1), ('thank', 1)]","[('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
771688054344089601,realDonaldTrump,"I visited our Trump Tower campaign headquarters last night, after returning from Ohio and Arizona, and it was packed with great pros - WIN!",False,2016-09-02T12:35:44,en,7267,29731,"[('visited', 1), ('trump', 1), ('tower', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('headquarters', 1)]","[('Trump Tower', 'ORG'), ('last night', 'TIME'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('Arizona', 'GPE')]"
771687247951298560,realDonaldTrump,People will be very surprised by our ground game on Nov. 8. We have an army of volunteers and people with GREAT SPIRIT! They want to #MAGA!,False,2016-09-02T12:32:31,en,9397,28792,"[('people', 2), ('surprised', 1), ('ground', 1), ('game', 1), ('nov', 1)]","[('Nov. 8', 'DATE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
771686352438042624,realDonaldTrump,Just heard that crazy and very dumb @morningmika had a mental breakdown while talking about me on the low ratings @Morning_Joe. Joe a mess!,False,2016-09-02T12:28:58,en,5944,21376,"[('joe', 2), ('heard', 1), ('crazy', 1), ('dumb', 1), ('morningmika', 1)]","[('Joe', 'PERSON')]"
771481226578460672,realDonaldTrump,I will be interviewed by @ericbolling tonight at 8pm on the @oreillyfactor. Enjoy!,False,2016-09-01T22:53:52,en,3945,15933,"[('interviewed', 1), ('ericbolling', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('pm', 1), ('oreillyfactor', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('8pm', 'TIME')]"
771393537900503040,realDonaldTrump,I am promising you a new legacy for America. We're going to create a new American future. Thank you OHIO! #ImWithYou https://t.co/TUgccsxvoy,False,2016-09-01T17:05:25,en,9741,29712,"[('new', 2), ('promising', 1), ('legacy', 1), ('america', 1), ('going', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('OHIO', 'ORG'), ('#', 'ORG')]"
771352519457005568,realDonaldTrump,Thank you for having me this morning @AmericanLegion. I enjoyed my time with everyone! #ALConvention2016 https://t.co/19TZEi6EbB,False,2016-09-01T14:22:26,en,6355,20610,"[('thank', 1), ('morning', 1), ('americanlegion', 1), ('enjoyed', 1), ('time', 1)]","[('this morning', 'TIME')]"
771298236376178688,realDonaldTrump,Poll numbers way up - making big progress!,False,2016-09-01T10:46:44,en,10162,38434,"[('poll', 1), ('number', 1), ('way', 1), ('making', 1), ('big', 1)]",[]
771296597963661312,realDonaldTrump,Thank you to @foxandfriends for the great review of the speech on immigration last night. Thank you also to the great people of Arizona!,False,2016-09-01T10:40:13,en,7082,29187,"[('thank', 2), ('great', 2), ('foxandfriends', 1), ('review', 1), ('speech', 1)]","[('last night', 'TIME'), ('Arizona', 'GPE')]"
771294347501461504,realDonaldTrump,Mexico will pay for the wall!,False,2016-09-01T10:31:17,en,30488,60574,"[('mexico', 1), ('pay', 1), ('wall', 1)]","[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
771212757517557760,realDonaldTrump,"Under a Trump administration, it's called #AmericaFirst! #ImWithYou
https://t.co/QfHfCQg0Wa",False,2016-09-01T05:07:04,en,8741,23629,"[('trump', 1), ('administration', 1), ('called', 1), ('americafirst', 1), ('imwithyou', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('#', 'ORG')]"
771212706275741696,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton doesn't have the strength or the stamina to MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN! #AmericaFirst
https://t.co/G1MuLrjhW9",False,2016-09-01T05:06:52,en,7138,20778,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('strength', 1), ('stamen', 1), ('make', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN', 'EVENT'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/G1MuLrjhW9', 'PERSON')]"
771210697552166913,realDonaldTrump,"There will be no amnesty!
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain #ImWithYou
https://t.co/vVhzSdCblA",False,2016-09-01T04:58:53,en,6504,18247,"[('amnesty', 1), ('makeamericagreatagain', 1), ('imwithyou', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
771210555822477313,realDonaldTrump,"Mexico will pay for the wall - 100%!
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain #ImWithYou
https://t.co/pSFuPZz0xP",False,2016-09-01T04:58:19,en,10340,23355,"[('mexico', 1), ('pay', 1), ('wall', 1), ('makeamericagreatagain', 1), ('imwithyou', 1)]","[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
771206171856207873,realDonaldTrump,We are Watching A Leader Who for the First Time in Three Presidencies Will Put America and Americans First! @realDonaldTrump #TrumpPence16,True,2016-09-01T04:40:54,en,9401,22030,"[('first', 2), ('watching', 1), ('leader', 1), ('time', 1), ('three', 1)]","[('Americans First', 'NORP'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
771206056454127616,realDonaldTrump,"I hear Churchill had a nice turn of phrase, but Trump's immigration speech is the most magnificent speech ever given.",True,2016-09-01T04:40:26,en,9105,24723,"[('speech', 2), ('hear', 1), ('churchill', 1), ('nice', 1), ('turn', 1)]","[('Churchill', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
771150050940497920,realDonaldTrump,"Just arrived in Arizona! #ImWithYou
https://t.co/MT3wW61YS5",False,2016-09-01T00:57:54,en,3322,15116,"[('arrived', 1), ('arizona', 1), ('imwithyou', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
771146302134423552,realDonaldTrump,Great trip to Mexico today  - wonderful leadership and high quality people! Look forward to our next meeting.,False,2016-09-01T00:43:00,en,10252,35958,"[('great', 1), ('trip', 1), ('mexico', 1), ('today', 1), ('wonderful', 1)]","[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
771145576381427712,realDonaldTrump,"Hillary Clinton didn't go to Louisiana, and now she didn't go to Mexico. She doesn't have the drive or stamina to MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!",False,2016-09-01T00:40:07,en,20890,57953,"[('go', 2), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('louisiana', 1), ('mexico', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN', 'EVENT')]"
770971306766381056,realDonaldTrump,"Former President Vicente Fox, who is railing against my visit to Mexico today, also invited me when he apologized for using the ""f bomb.""",False,2016-08-31T13:07:38,en,10898,30972,"[('former', 1), ('president', 1), ('vicente', 1), ('fox', 1), ('railing', 1)]","[('Vicente Fox', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
770832664303587328,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you Washington! Together, WE will MAKE AMERICA SAFE AND GREAT AGAIN! #ImWithYou #AmericaFirst https://t.co/CWDQnISYH4",False,2016-08-31T03:56:43,en,9636,28252,"[('thank', 1), ('washington', 1), ('together', 1), ('make', 1), ('america', 1)]","[('Washington', 'GPE'), ('AmericaFirst', 'ORG')]"
770811688966770689,realDonaldTrump,"I have accepted the invitation of President Enrique Pena Nieto, of Mexico, and look very much forward to meeting him tomorrow.",False,2016-08-31T02:33:22,en,20696,56438,"[('accepted', 1), ('invitation', 1), ('president', 1), ('enrique', 1), ('pena', 1)]","[('Enrique Pena Nieto', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE')]"
770807738104328192,realDonaldTrump,"We are ALREADY LIVE in Everett, WA for the Trump Rally. Come join us- our cameras tonight! #TrumpinEverett 

https://t.co/RQdUpI6mnw",True,2016-08-31T02:17:40,en,2273,7882,"[('already', 1), ('live', 1), ('everett', 1), ('wa', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('the Trump Rally', 'ORG'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('TrumpinEverett', 'PRODUCT')]"
770806857271091201,realDonaldTrump,"REUTERS POLL:  CLINTON, TRUMP ALL TIED UP... https://t.co/htCXcTA5T7",True,2016-08-31T02:14:10,en,3609,8479,"[('reuters', 1), ('poll', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('trump', 1), ('tied', 1)]",[]
770771735092142080,realDonaldTrump,Thank you North Carolina! #MAGA https://t.co/1oWrFnHe0u,False,2016-08-30T23:54:36,en,7694,23570,"[('thank', 1), ('north', 1), ('carolina', 1), ('maga', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('North Carolina', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
770724546454417408,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you America! #MAGA
https://t.co/FljBVvbwKr https://t.co/ePJW9jLckM",False,2016-08-30T20:47:05,en,8049,22226,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('thank', 1), ('america', 1), ('maga', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
770573355191631873,realDonaldTrump,"""@meequalsfree: Looking forward to seeing you again! Everett to be a packed house! @realDonaldTrump  @mike_pence""",False,2016-08-30T10:46:19,en,3327,12346,"[('meequalsfree', 1), ('looking', 1), ('forward', 1), ('seeing', 1), ('everett', 1)]","[('Everett', 'PERSON')]"
770568584443539456,realDonaldTrump,"From day one I said that I was going to build a great wall on the SOUTHERN BORDER, and much more. Stop illegal immigration. Watch Wednesday!",False,2016-08-30T10:27:21,en,11342,34473,"[('day', 1), ('one', 1), ('said', 1), ('going', 1), ('build', 1)]","[('day one', 'DATE'), ('the SOUTHERN BORDER', 'LOC'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
770417590351040513,realDonaldTrump,"Join me this Thursday in Wilmington, Ohio at noon! #ImWithYou
Tickets: https://t.co/66bfVtIwf1 https://t.co/fDAJl5wVGe",False,2016-08-30T00:27:21,en,5119,14366,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('thursday', 1), ('wilmington', 1)]","[('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Wilmington', 'GPE'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('noon', 'TIME')]"
770414693869649921,realDonaldTrump,"Join me this Wednesday in Phoenix, Arizona at 6pm! #ImWithYou
Tickets: https://t.co/1jATILh2k7 https://t.co/VwKnxo1TNQ",False,2016-08-30T00:15:51,en,4746,12933,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('wednesday', 1), ('phoenix', 1)]","[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Phoenix', 'GPE'), ('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
770381482229657602,realDonaldTrump,We will repeal and replace the horrible disaster known as #Obamacare! https://t.co/YzRTPrqrNC,False,2016-08-29T22:03:53,en,10661,25394,"[('repeal', 1), ('replace', 1), ('horrible', 1), ('disaster', 1), ('known', 1)]","[('Obamacare', 'ORG')]"
770253550639251456,realDonaldTrump,"Now that African-Americans are seeing what a bad job Hillary type policy and management has done to the inner-cities, they want TRUMP!",False,2016-08-29T13:35:31,en,9064,28368,"[('african', 1), ('american', 1), ('seeing', 1), ('bad', 1), ('job', 1)]","[('African-Americans', 'NORP'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('TRUMP', 'ORG')]"
770252177512230912,realDonaldTrump,"Crooked Hillary's brainpower is highly overrated.Probably why her decision making is so bad or, as stated by Bernie S, she has BAD JUDGEMENT",False,2016-08-29T13:30:04,en,7242,22910,"[('bad', 2), ('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('brainpower', 1), ('highly', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Bernie S', 'PERSON')]"
770250409843777536,realDonaldTrump,"Does anyone know that Crooked Hillary, who tried so hard, was unable to pass the Bar Exams in Washington D.C. She was forced to go elsewhere",False,2016-08-29T13:23:02,en,10941,30830,"[('anyone', 1), ('know', 1), ('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('tried', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('the Bar Exams', 'ORG'), ('Washington D.C.', 'GPE')]"
770249086255661056,realDonaldTrump,"""@PMNOrlando: @realDonaldTrump I know of NO ONE voting for Crooked Hillary! Her rallies are held in (blank)  &amp; she still has room.",False,2016-08-29T13:17:47,en,4324,14105,"[('pmnorlando', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('know', 1), ('one', 1), ('voting', 1)]","[('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
770248548571021312,realDonaldTrump,"""@RhondaR: Thank-You Clarence Henderson for telling @cnn you know racism &amp; it's not DonaldTrump https://t.co/fSBPxZU8Gu via @BreitbartNews""",False,2016-08-29T13:15:39,en,6903,16429,"[('rhondar', 1), ('thank', 1), ('clarence', 1), ('henderson', 1), ('telling', 1)]","[('@cnn', 'ORG'), ('DonaldTrump', 'ORG')]"
770248186241900544,realDonaldTrump,"""@Patrici: Crowd at Trump Rally in Akron, Ohio is a Sea of Women, Minorities, Independents, Dems https://t.co/wm7HV8WPGk via @gatewaypundit",False,2016-08-29T13:14:12,en,6675,16177,"[('patrici', 1), ('crowd', 1), ('trump', 1), ('rally', 1), ('akron', 1)]","[('Trump Rally in Akron', 'ORG'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('a Sea of Women', 'LOC'), ('Independents', 'NORP'), ('Dems', 'NORP')]"
770247094439469058,realDonaldTrump,Inner-city crime is reaching record levels. African-Americans will vote for Trump because they know I will stop the slaughter going on!,False,2016-08-29T13:09:52,en,6911,21395,"[('inner', 1), ('city', 1), ('crime', 1), ('reaching', 1), ('record', 1)]","[('African-Americans', 'NORP')]"
770245313345052673,realDonaldTrump,"Look how bad it is getting! How much more crime, how many more shootings, will it take for African-Americans and Latinos to vote Trump=SAFE!",False,2016-08-29T13:02:47,en,7080,22710,"[('look', 1), ('bad', 1), ('getting', 1), ('much', 1), ('crime', 1)]","[('African-Americans', 'NORP'), ('Latinos', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
770040258796855296,realDonaldTrump,"I will be making a major speech on ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION on Wednesday in the GREAT State of Arizona. Big crowds, looking for a larger venue.",False,2016-08-28T23:27:59,en,10687,33919,"[('making', 1), ('major', 1), ('speech', 1), ('illegal', 1), ('immigration', 1)]","[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('the GREAT State', 'FAC'), ('Arizona', 'GPE')]"
770039317142069248,realDonaldTrump,"I think that both candidates, Crooked Hillary and myself, should release detailed medical records. I have no problem in doing so! Hillary?",False,2016-08-28T23:24:14,en,20209,53474,"[('hillary', 2), ('think', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('crooked', 1), ('release', 1)]","[('Crooked Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
770021252002119680,realDonaldTrump,"Today is the 53rd anniversary of the March on Washington - today we honor the enduring fight for justice, equality and opportunity.",False,2016-08-28T22:12:27,en,8754,29187,"[('today', 2), ('rd', 1), ('anniversary', 1), ('march', 1), ('washington', 1)]","[('Today', 'DATE'), ('53rd', 'ORDINAL'), ('March', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
769980181633204224,realDonaldTrump,Poll: @realDonaldTrump vs. @HillaryClinton among white Evangelicals. https://t.co/6ohwIh1Q24,True,2016-08-28T19:29:15,en,9029,22461,"[('poll', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('v', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('among', 1)]","[('@realDonaldTrump', 'PERSON'), ('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON')]"
769898524439896064,realDonaldTrump,Thank you Arizona! #VoteTrump https://t.co/v8VLxdd0fO,False,2016-08-28T14:04:46,en,6303,21328,"[('thank', 1), ('arizona', 1), ('votetrump', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('VoteTrump', 'MONEY')]"
769897797319532544,realDonaldTrump,"Join me Tuesday in Everett, Washington at the Xfinity Arena! Tickets: https://t.co/ABQGySdcYt https://t.co/sn08gnd0lq",False,2016-08-28T14:01:53,en,4409,12516,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('tuesday', 1), ('everett', 1)]","[('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Everett', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('the Xfinity Arena', 'ORG')]"
769740626497679360,realDonaldTrump,"""@LindaHarden: @realDonaldTrump America loves Trump and @mike_pence -- praying for you every day. Stay strong. #TrumpPence2016 #NeverHillary",False,2016-08-28T03:37:21,en,4826,16279,"[('lindaharden', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('america', 1), ('love', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('NeverHillary', 'ORG')]"
769724556949020672,realDonaldTrump,"NATIONAL DEBT 
January 2009 = $10.6 TRILLION
August 2016 = $19.4 TRILLION https://t.co/dKAVaLfGAJ",False,2016-08-28T02:33:29,en,12572,22952,"[('trillion', 2), ('national', 1), ('debt', 1), ('january', 1), ('august', 1)]","[('NATIONAL DEBT \r\n', 'ORG'), ('January 2009', 'DATE'), ('$10.6 TRILLION\r\n', 'MONEY'), ('August 2016', 'DATE'), ('$19.4 TRILLION', 'MONEY')]"
769718184836472832,realDonaldTrump,It was an honor to have the amazing Root family join me in Iowa. I have been so inspired by their courage &amp; bravery. https://t.co/P4qVGGUYVZ,False,2016-08-28T02:08:10,en,7224,21728,"[('honor', 1), ('amazing', 1), ('root', 1), ('family', 1), ('join', 1)]","[('Iowa', 'GPE')]"
769647461459632128,realDonaldTrump,Thank you Iowa! #ImWithYou https://t.co/3BIF6jBTkk,False,2016-08-27T21:27:08,en,5933,19460,"[('thank', 1), ('iowa', 1), ('imwithyou', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('Iowa', 'GPE'), ('#', 'ORG')]"
769607369869266944,realDonaldTrump,Just landed in Iowa to attend a great event in honor of wonderful Senator @JoniErnst. Look forward to being with all of my friends.,False,2016-08-27T18:47:50,en,4413,17915,"[('landed', 1), ('iowa', 1), ('attend', 1), ('great', 1), ('event', 1)]","[('Iowa', 'GPE')]"
769592508879892480,realDonaldTrump,"My condolences to Dwyane Wade and his family, on the loss of Nykea Aldridge. They are in my thoughts and prayers.",False,2016-08-27T17:48:47,en,9157,31598,"[('condolence', 1), ('dwyane', 1), ('wade', 1), ('family', 1), ('loss', 1)]","[('Nykea Aldridge', 'ORG')]"
769571710924263424,realDonaldTrump,Dwyane Wade's cousin was just shot and killed walking her baby in Chicago. Just what I have been saying. African-Americans will VOTE TRUMP!,False,2016-08-27T16:26:08,en,9419,28129,"[('dwyane', 1), ('wade', 1), ('cousin', 1), ('shot', 1), ('killed', 1)]","[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('African-Americans', 'NORP')]"
769554782151331840,realDonaldTrump,"""@GoldJazz559: #BlackMenForBernie Leader: #Hillary2016 ‘No Regard For Black Race’ https://t.co/m8952Ly3Jb via @dailycaller #BlacksForTrump",False,2016-08-27T15:18:52,en,4626,10727,"[('goldjazz', 1), ('blackmenforbernie', 1), ('leader', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('regard', 1)]","[('BlackMenForBernie', 'ORG')]"
769552592158412800,realDonaldTrump,"""@DiamondandSilk: Crooked Hillary getting desperate. On TV bashing Trump. @CNN, she forgot how she said a KKK member was her mentor.",False,2016-08-27T15:10:10,en,9261,22512,"[('diamondandsilk', 1), ('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('getting', 1), ('desperate', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('KKK', 'GPE')]"
769539271678013440,realDonaldTrump,Heroin overdoses are taking over our children and others in the MIDWEST. Coming in from our southern border. We need strong border &amp; WALL!,False,2016-08-27T14:17:14,en,11641,35050,"[('border', 2), ('heroin', 1), ('overdoses', 1), ('taking', 1), ('child', 1)]","[('MIDWEST', 'LOC')]"
769331841316687873,realDonaldTrump,"New polls - join the MOVEMENT today.
https://t.co/3KWOl20zMm #ImWithYou https://t.co/numII7W99T",False,2016-08-27T00:32:59,en,11925,27151,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('new', 1), ('poll', 1), ('join', 1)]","[('#', 'ORG')]"
769323472048623616,realDonaldTrump,Join us via our new #AmericaFirst APP! #TrumpPence16 https://t.co/FccLQSCkDY https://t.co/0angXB2BrI,False,2016-08-26T23:59:43,en,4833,12694,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('join', 1), ('u', 1), ('via', 1)]","[('AmericaFirst', 'ORG'), ('#TrumpPence16 https://t.co/FccLQSCkDY', 'PERCENT')]"
769322071297888257,realDonaldTrump,"Will be in Phoenix, Arizona on Wednesday. Changing venue to much larger one. Demand is unreal. Polls looking great! #ImWithYou",False,2016-08-26T23:54:09,en,7502,23594,"[('phoenix', 1), ('arizona', 1), ('wednesday', 1), ('changing', 1), ('venue', 1)]","[('Phoenix', 'GPE'), ('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
769311305480024065,realDonaldTrump,"Thank you @TeamTrump Florida. Keep me updated, and lets get those 100,000 registered voters!
#MakeAmericaGreatAgain  https://t.co/lseAAqxjA9",False,2016-08-26T23:11:22,en,5135,14682,"[('thank', 1), ('teamtrump', 1), ('florida', 1), ('keep', 1), ('updated', 1)]","[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('100,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
769308316350623744,realDonaldTrump,"I will be interviewed by @kimguilfoyle 
at 7pm on @FoxNews. #Enjoy!",False,2016-08-26T22:59:30,en,2482,10737,"[('interviewed', 1), ('kimguilfoyle', 1), ('pm', 1), ('foxnews', 1), ('enjoy', 1)]","[('7pm', 'TIME')]"
769254655939321857,realDonaldTrump,Army training slide lists Hillary Clinton as insider threat: https://t.co/CQTSo2ETJF,False,2016-08-26T19:26:16,en,8609,17210,"[('army', 1), ('training', 1), ('slide', 1), ('list', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Army', 'ORG'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
769253422549786628,realDonaldTrump,Meet the ‘Trumpocrats’: Lifelong Democrats Breaking w/ Party Over Hillary to Support Donald Trump for President: https://t.co/g2N3JJWV8a,False,2016-08-26T19:21:22,en,7986,19172,"[('meet', 1), ('trumpocrats', 1), ('lifelong', 1), ('democrat', 1), ('breaking', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Support Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
769252637350866946,realDonaldTrump,"""Hillary Clinton Deleted Emails Using Program Intended To Prevent Recovery"" #CrookedHillary https://t.co/D0MeBJXBwN",False,2016-08-26T19:18:15,en,8405,16274,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('deleted', 1), ('email', 1), ('using', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton Deleted Emails Using Program Intended To Prevent', 'PERSON')]"
769221405820923905,realDonaldTrump,"How quickly people forget that Crooked Hillary called African-American youth ""SUPER PREDATORS"" - Has she apologized?",False,2016-08-26T17:14:09,en,13148,28591,"[('quickly', 1), ('people', 1), ('forget', 1), ('crooked', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('African-American', 'NORP'), ('SUPER', 'ORG')]"
769203012250112006,realDonaldTrump,I am very proud to have brought the subject of illegal immigration back into the discussion. Such a big problem for our country-I will solve,False,2016-08-26T16:01:03,en,9150,32425,"[('proud', 1), ('brought', 1), ('subject', 1), ('illegal', 1), ('immigration', 1)]",[]
769185155198124032,realDonaldTrump,Wonderful @pastormarkburns was attacked viciously and unfairly on @MSNBC by crazy @morningmika on low ratings @Morning_Joe. Apologize!,False,2016-08-26T14:50:06,en,5733,15118,"[('wonderful', 1), ('pastormarkburns', 1), ('attacked', 1), ('viciously', 1), ('unfairly', 1)]","[('@MSNBC', 'ORG')]"
