id,handle,text,is_retweet,time,lang,retweet_count,favorite_count,filtered_text,entities
780925634159796224,HillaryClinton,The question in this election: Who can put the plans into action that will make your life better? https://t.co/XreEY9OicG,False,2016-09-28T00:22:34,en,218,651,"[('question', 1), ('election', 1), ('put', 1), ('plan', 1), ('action', 1)]",[]
780916180899037184,HillaryClinton,"Last night, Donald Trump said not paying taxes was ""smart."" You know what I call it? Unpatriotic. https://t.co/t0xmBfj7zF",True,2016-09-27T23:45:00,en,2445,5308,"[('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('said', 1)]","[('Last night', 'TIME'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780911564857761793,HillaryClinton,Couldn't be more proud of @HillaryClinton. Her vision and command during last night's debate showed that she's ready to be our next @POTUS.,True,2016-09-27T23:26:40,en,7834,27234,"[('proud', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('vision', 1), ('command', 1), ('last', 1)]","[(""last night's"", 'TIME'), ('@POTUS', 'ORG')]"
780907038650068994,HillaryClinton,"If we stand together, there's nothing we can't do. 

Make sure you're ready to vote: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/Q3Ymbb7UNy",False,2016-09-27T23:08:41,en,916,2542,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('stand', 1), ('together', 1), ('nothing', 1)]",[]
780897419462602752,HillaryClinton,Both candidates were asked about how they'd confront racial injustice. Only one had a real answer. https://t.co/sjnEokckis,False,2016-09-27T22:30:27,en,859,2882,"[('candidate', 1), ('asked', 1), ('confront', 1), ('racial', 1), ('injustice', 1)]","[('Only one', 'CARDINAL')]"
780883582051123200,HillaryClinton,This election is too important to sit out. Go to https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm and make sure you're registered. #NationalVoterRegistrationDay -H,False,2016-09-27T21:35:28,en,1303,2849,"[('election', 1), ('important', 1), ('sit', 1), ('go', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
780881075891531776,HillaryClinton,When Donald Trump goes low...register to vote: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/DXz9dEwsZS,False,2016-09-27T21:25:31,en,1833,4954,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('go', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780874710049550336,HillaryClinton,3) Has Trump offered a single proposal to reduce the friction of starting a business. @HillaryClinton has https://t.co/OhFAFEFsUq,True,2016-09-27T21:00:13,en,1087,2824,"[('trump', 1), ('offered', 1), ('single', 1), ('proposal', 1), ('reduce', 1)]","[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
780869063648153601,HillaryClinton,"The election is just weeks away. Check if you're registered to vote at https://t.co/HcMAh8ljR0, only takes a few cl… https://t.co/H1H7hAA4XM",True,2016-09-27T20:37:47,en,3347,7698,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('h', 2), ('election', 1), ('week', 1)]","[('just weeks', 'DATE')]"
780859420846727168,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump lied to the American people at least 58 times during the first presidential debate. (We counted.) https://t.co/h43O6Rws4S,False,2016-09-27T19:59:28,en,5379,8917,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('lied', 1), ('american', 1), ('people', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('at least 58', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
780852261442445312,HillaryClinton,"“She gained about 55 pounds in...9 months. She was like an eating machine.” —Trump, a man who wants to be president: https://t.co/1ht91eZCyw",False,2016-09-27T19:31:01,en,2058,3714,"[('gained', 1), ('pound', 1), ('month', 1), ('like', 1), ('eating', 1)]","[('about 55 pounds', 'QUANTITY'), ('...9 months', 'DATE')]"
780840847256453120,HillaryClinton,It's #NationalVoterRegistrationDay. Celebrate by registering to vote → https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/R6lVvgLECG,False,2016-09-27T18:45:39,en,1792,3500,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('nationalvoterregistrationday', 1), ('celebrate', 1), ('registering', 1)]",[]
780832403392790529,HillaryClinton,"""I love this country.
I’m proud of this country.
I want to be a leader who brings people together.""
—Hillary #LoveTrumpsHate",False,2016-09-27T18:12:06,en,1437,5053,"[('country', 2), ('love', 1), ('proud', 1), ('want', 1), ('leader', 1)]",[]
780831901204484097,HillaryClinton,"We don’t want to turn against each other.
We want to work with one another.
We want to set big goals in this country.
#StrongerTogether",False,2016-09-27T18:10:07,en,976,3313,"[('want', 3), ('turn', 1), ('work', 1), ('one', 1), ('another', 1)]",[]
780830984262516736,HillaryClinton,"""What we hear from my opponent is dangerously incoherent. It's unclear what he's saying, but words matter."" —Hillary",False,2016-09-27T18:06:28,en,957,2968,"[('hear', 1), ('opponent', 1), ('dangerously', 1), ('incoherent', 1), ('unclear', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780830729760485378,HillaryClinton,One candidate made it clear he wasn’t prepared for last night’s debate. The other made it clear she’s prepared to b… https://t.co/InYZBmnbBM,False,2016-09-27T18:05:27,en,3336,9961,"[('made', 2), ('clear', 2), ('prepared', 2), ('one', 1), ('candidate', 1)]","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('last night', 'TIME')]"
780830087457406980,HillaryClinton,"""What kind of a person would want to root for 9 million families losing their homes?

One who should never be president."" —Hillary on Trump",False,2016-09-27T18:02:54,en,1127,3216,"[('kind', 1), ('person', 1), ('would', 1), ('want', 1), ('root', 1)]","[('9 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780828916919504896,HillaryClinton,"""I don’t think that any family should have to pay more than 10% of their income on child care.” —Hillary https://t.co/pepW0auI8n",False,2016-09-27T17:58:15,en,586,1681,"[('think', 1), ('family', 1), ('pay', 1), ('income', 1), ('child', 1)]","[('more than 10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780828206039502848,HillaryClinton,"""I’m really glad my dad never had a contract with Donald Trump.” —Hillary https://t.co/un2YiRLEYF",False,2016-09-27T17:55:26,en,1580,2967,"[('really', 1), ('glad', 1), ('dad', 1), ('never', 1), ('contract', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780827541670076416,HillaryClinton,"When you work hard, you should not be living in poverty. https://t.co/86sTOCAkkq",False,2016-09-27T17:52:47,en,557,1633,"[('work', 1), ('hard', 1), ('living', 1), ('poverty', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
780825360611086336,HillaryClinton,"""We may have a record-setting turnout in this election.

We could have the biggest turnout we've ever had."" https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm",False,2016-09-27T17:44:07,en,556,1546,"[('turnout', 2), ('may', 1), ('record', 1), ('setting', 1), ('election', 1)]",[]
780824346310877184,HillaryClinton,"""You can go to https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm to make sure you are registered. And I hope you all will.” —Hillary #NationalVoterRegistrationDay",False,2016-09-27T17:40:05,en,661,1326,"[('go', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('ttgeqxnqym', 1), ('make', 1)]",[]
780823097498796034,HillaryClinton,Join Hillary live in NC for her first rally since winning last night's debate → https://t.co/DzEpIDf7HY #NationalVoterRegistrationDay,False,2016-09-27T17:35:08,en,1115,3941,"[('join', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('live', 1), ('nc', 1), ('first', 1)]","[('Join Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('NC', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), (""last night's"", 'TIME')]"
780819344553107456,HillaryClinton,So. Everything you're feeling after #Debates2016? It's #NationalVoterRegistrationDay. PLEASE:… https://t.co/YnOtJL8bW7,True,2016-09-27T17:20:13,en,1328,2435,"[('everything', 1), ('feeling', 1), ('debate', 1), ('nationalvoterregistrationday', 1), ('please', 1)]",[]
780816109700124672,HillaryClinton,"“Donald just criticized me for preparing for this debate. And you know what else I prepared for?

I prepared to be… https://t.co/QjB01msPaT",False,2016-09-27T17:07:22,en,6185,16805,"[('prepared', 2), ('donald', 1), ('criticized', 1), ('preparing', 1), ('debate', 1)]","[('Donald', 'PERSON')]"
780812840529723392,HillaryClinton,Hillary was the winner of the first presidential debate—and newspapers across America agree. #SheWon… https://t.co/oDiUHd0eXO,False,2016-09-27T16:54:22,en,2593,6269,"[('hillary', 1), ('winner', 1), ('first', 1), ('presidential', 1), ('debate', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('SheWon', 'PERSON')]"
780806581650878464,HillaryClinton,Register and vote for Democrats like @HillaryClinton and @KatieMcGintyPA: https://t.co/tu6W6eS9xR #iRegistered… https://t.co/9ovdecqadN,True,2016-09-27T16:29:30,en,1235,3206,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('register', 1), ('vote', 1), ('democrat', 1)]","[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON'), ('@KatieMcGintyPA', 'ORG'), ('https://t.co/tu6W6eS9xR #iRegistered', 'ORG')]"
780805211472486401,HillaryClinton,I've been fortunate to meet young Americans from all over the country. We all make choices. This is mine...… https://t.co/bYoUE91TOO,True,2016-09-27T16:24:03,en,804,2086,"[('fortunate', 1), ('meet', 1), ('young', 1), ('american', 1), ('country', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
780802294002647040,HillaryClinton,"""She gained a massive amount of weight...it was a real problem."" —Trump this morning on Alicia Machado https://t.co/LJPlFegSTs",False,2016-09-27T16:12:28,en,4829,7580,"[('gained', 1), ('massive', 1), ('amount', 1), ('weight', 1), ('real', 1)]","[('this morning', 'TIME'), ('Alicia Machado', 'PERSON')]"
780800117867683841,HillaryClinton,"Today is #NationalVoterRegistrationDay - I was beaten, left bloody &amp; unconscious so that every person could register and vote. Do your part.",True,2016-09-27T16:03:49,en,20006,24333,"[('today', 1), ('nationalvoterregistrationday', 1), ('beaten', 1), ('left', 1), ('bloody', 1)]","[('Today', 'DATE')]"
780799428269670400,HillaryClinton,More than 70 million Americans aren't registered to vote. We have to do better! Get registered &amp; spread the word: https://t.co/IobF5PQ7jv,True,2016-09-27T16:01:04,en,1138,1554,"[('registered', 2), ('million', 1), ('american', 1), ('vote', 1), ('better', 1)]","[('More than 70 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
780797677009244160,HillaryClinton,"When you have a really, really good night. #SheWon https://t.co/FVeGqhYxRZ",False,2016-09-27T15:54:07,en,8242,35744,"[('really', 2), ('good', 1), ('night', 1), ('shewon', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
780794828007305217,HillaryClinton,"""Register. Vote. Go out and get engaged!” —@JoeBiden #NationalVoterRegistrationDay https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm",False,2016-09-27T15:42:48,en,1350,2874,"[('register', 1), ('vote', 1), ('go', 1), ('get', 1), ('engaged', 1)]",[]
780792352214573057,HillaryClinton,"""I'm glad Trump found out that Crimea was part of Ukraine. By the way, I heard he was on the verge of acknowledging gravity."" —@JoeBiden",False,2016-09-27T15:32:57,en,5557,16289,"[('glad', 1), ('trump', 1), ('found', 1), ('crimea', 1), ('part', 1)]","[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Crimea', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
780790673851224064,HillaryClinton,"“Let me tell you who built this damn country: the middle class.” —@JoeBiden

Let's keep building it, together: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm",False,2016-09-27T15:26:17,en,1453,4741,"[('let', 2), ('tell', 1), ('built', 1), ('damn', 1), ('country', 1)]",[]
780787312460464129,HillaryClinton,One moment last night that proved—again—that Hillary's the only candidate ready to lead on the global stage: https://t.co/i4lrw7BpE9 #SheWon,False,2016-09-27T15:12:56,en,1452,4840,"[('one', 1), ('moment', 1), ('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('proved', 1)]","[('One moment last night', 'TIME'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('SheWon', 'MONEY')]"
780782299524792320,HillaryClinton,"""Anyone who complains about microphone problems is not having a good night."" —Hillary #SheWon",False,2016-09-27T14:53:01,en,4773,14979,"[('anyone', 1), ('complains', 1), ('microphone', 1), ('problem', 1), ('good', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('SheWon', 'ORG')]"
780768433910710272,HillaryClinton,"Trump on Alicia, 1996: ""Miss Piggy.""

This morning: ""She gained a massive amount of weight...it was a real problem."" https://t.co/0wrISjJe6z",False,2016-09-27T13:57:55,en,16476,22611,"[('trump', 1), ('alicia', 1), ('miss', 1), ('piggy', 1), ('morning', 1)]","[('1996', 'DATE'), ('Piggy', 'PERSON'), ('This morning', 'TIME')]"
780746901591199744,HillaryClinton,"""I have a winning temperament."" —Donald Trump last night 

Really? #SheWon https://t.co/nMTFoISagO",False,2016-09-27T12:32:21,en,4120,10456,"[('winning', 1), ('temperament', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('last', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('last night', 'TIME')]"
780738162880634880,HillaryClinton,Only one person on last night's stage is prepared to be Commander-in-Chief. Make sure she gets the chance:… https://t.co/o50AezGRrb,False,2016-09-27T11:57:38,en,6253,17113,"[('one', 1), ('person', 1), ('last', 1), ('night', 1), ('stage', 1)]","[('Only one', 'CARDINAL'), (""last night's"", 'TIME'), ('https://t.co/o50AezGRrb', 'ORG')]"
780637326921830400,HillaryClinton,"Tonight, @HillaryClinton proved she is ready to be President — and Donald Trump proved he is not. #debatenight https://t.co/Zeq5iF09Bc",True,2016-09-27T05:16:56,en,10733,30012,"[('proved', 2), ('tonight', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('ready', 1), ('president', 1)]","[('Tonight', 'TIME'), ('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/Zeq5iF09Bc', 'ORG')]"
780619128210087937,HillaryClinton,43 days left. Let’s go win this thing: https://t.co/vJShYQPqJb #DebateNight https://t.co/MzR30MEI0J,False,2016-09-27T04:04:38,en,6505,21912,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('day', 1), ('left', 1), ('let', 1)]","[('43 days', 'DATE'), ('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780616114120294400,HillaryClinton,.@timkaine That's what we @Wellesley girls do! And it's so clear @HillaryClinton is the only candidate prepared to be president #debatenight,True,2016-09-27T03:52:39,en,3229,10833,"[('timkaine', 1), ('wellesley', 1), ('girl', 1), ('clear', 1), ('hillaryclinton', 1)]","[('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON')]"
780611407221960704,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump called her ""Miss Piggy"" and ""Miss Housekeeping.""

Her name is Alicia Machado. #DebateNight https://t.co/0wrISjJe6z",False,2016-09-27T03:33:57,en,57182,74103,"[('miss', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('called', 1), ('piggy', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Miss Housekeeping', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Alicia Machado', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780607486516690944,HillaryClinton,Hillary Clinton did what she needed to do: https://t.co/OhN5ZjCu2G https://t.co/4P3f6pNXB3,True,2016-09-27T03:18:22,en,2277,6913,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('needed', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
780606592337252352,HillaryClinton,"Tonight, we heard from two candidates -- but only one president. #ImWithHer",True,2016-09-27T03:14:49,en,7576,20896,"[('tonight', 1), ('heard', 1), ('two', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('one', 1)]","[('Tonight', 'TIME'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('only one', 'CARDINAL')]"
780606012667691008,HillaryClinton,"""Hillary won big time. It was a shut out."" -- @HardballChris #debatenight",True,2016-09-27T03:12:31,en,4682,12991,"[('hillary', 1), ('big', 1), ('time', 1), ('shut', 1), ('hardballchris', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780603720191148032,HillaryClinton,Clinton won this debate in part because she had more stamina for this than Trump. He flagged badly after 30 minutes. She didn't.,True,2016-09-27T03:03:24,en,8546,22141,"[('clinton', 1), ('debate', 1), ('part', 1), ('stamen', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('30 minutes', 'TIME')]"
780602342890737664,HillaryClinton,The presidency isn't a reality show—it's as real as it gets. Make sure you're registered to vote:… https://t.co/gBZ42fzFnF,False,2016-09-27T02:57:56,en,8550,20188,"[('presidency', 1), ('reality', 1), ('show', 1), ('real', 1), ('get', 1)]",[]
780600557325156353,HillaryClinton,Text IMWITHHER to 47246 to tell Hillary you're on her team all the way to Election Day. #debatenight https://t.co/YzlkvzVTGY,False,2016-09-27T02:50:50,en,3134,12026,"[('text', 1), ('imwithher', 1), ('tell', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('team', 1)]","[('47246', 'DATE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Election Day', 'DATE')]"
780599274384027648,HillaryClinton,RT this if you're proud to be standing with Hillary tonight. #debatenight https://t.co/91tBmKxVMs,False,2016-09-27T02:45:44,en,80169,80678,"[('rt', 1), ('proud', 1), ('standing', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('tonight', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780598650628169729,HillaryClinton,Hillary just proved she's the only candidate who's ready to be president. Chip in now and let's go win this thing: https://t.co/ATqqxWU0Hc,False,2016-09-27T02:43:15,en,5065,16336,"[('hillary', 1), ('proved', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('ready', 1), ('president', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780597846814982144,HillaryClinton,"When Donald Trump says he has a ""winning temperament."" #debatenight https://t.co/ElQ7aG2vxu",False,2016-09-27T02:40:04,en,26656,48875,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('say', 1), ('winning', 1), ('temperament', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780597333650239488,HillaryClinton,The woman Trump called “Miss Piggy” has a name: Alicia. #debatenight https://t.co/XlthzE8X8j,False,2016-09-27T02:38:01,en,23394,36574,"[('woman', 1), ('trump', 1), ('called', 1), ('miss', 1), ('piggy', 1)]","[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780595314210267137,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump's ""cavalier attitude about nuclear weapons is so deeply troubling.” #DebateNight https://t.co/z66rUZz31J",False,2016-09-27T02:30:00,en,5011,13026,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('cavalier', 1), ('attitude', 1), ('nuclear', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780594655318638592,HillaryClinton,.@realDonaldTrump: Barack Obama is your president too. #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T02:27:23,en,17402,38775,"[('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('barack', 1), ('obama', 1), ('president', 1), ('debatenight', 1)]","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
780594447427960833,HillaryClinton,A man who can be provoked by a tweet should not have his hands anywhere near the nuclear codes. #DebateNight,False,2016-09-27T02:26:33,en,45008,82338,"[('man', 1), ('provoked', 1), ('tweet', 1), ('hand', 1), ('anywhere', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780594312182657024,HillaryClinton,This should go without saying: Taking nuclear war lightly is disqualifying for anyone seeking to be President of th… https://t.co/OXigxJhmqJ,False,2016-09-27T02:26:01,en,5820,13113,"[('go', 1), ('without', 1), ('saying', 1), ('taking', 1), ('nuclear', 1)]",[]
780593967737999361,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump says he has better temperament than Hillary Clinton.

Fact check: He is Donald Trump. 

780592331368128512,HillaryClinton,"""I hope the fact-checkers are turning up the volume. Donald Trump supported the invasion of Iraq.” https://t.co/CoyJtoyxd0",False,2016-09-27T02:18:09,en,7062,12598,"[('hope', 1), ('fact', 1), ('checker', 1), ('turning', 1), ('volume', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iraq', 'GPE')]"
780592014639456256,HillaryClinton,This is... still not true! #debate https://t.co/6SKFZunCL5,True,2016-09-27T02:16:53,en,1387,2339,"[('still', 1), ('true', 1), ('debate', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]","[('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
780591277620551680,HillaryClinton,What is the deal with Donald Trump and Russia? https://t.co/xUYxOdoYo3 #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T02:13:57,en,2540,4893,"[('deal', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('russia', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
780591186046222336,HillaryClinton,Trump's top Russia advisor is being probed for meeting with the Kremlin aide in charge of US election intelligence.  https://t.co/GN5Gg4ug0L,True,2016-09-27T02:13:36,en,1213,1638,"[('trump', 1), ('top', 1), ('russia', 1), ('advisor', 1), ('probed', 1)]","[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
780589899518967808,HillaryClinton,"When Donald Trump goes low, we go high. #DebateNight https://t.co/5MUlOMJqWM",False,2016-09-27T02:08:29,en,6189,16416,"[('go', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('low', 1), ('high', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780589488271687681,HillaryClinton,"When a man is sued for discriminating against black tenants &amp; pushes birtherism, he's giving you an idea of what kind of president he'd be.",False,2016-09-27T02:06:51,en,13915,26574,"[('man', 1), ('sued', 1), ('discriminating', 1), ('black', 1), ('tenant', 1)]",[]
780589100483145728,HillaryClinton,This is just one of the business practices that led to Donald Trump being sued for discrimination. #Debate… https://t.co/PoXvMnGfCy,True,2016-09-27T02:05:18,en,1523,1946,"[('one', 1), ('business', 1), ('practice', 1), ('led', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
780588840201388032,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump's answer for his five years of pushing the racist birther conspiracy theory?

""I say nothing."" #debatenight",False,2016-09-27T02:04:16,en,6274,13551,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('answer', 1), ('five', 1), ('year', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('his five years', 'DATE')]"
780588262402424832,HillaryClinton,"""Trump just criticized me for preparing for this debate. You know what else I prepared for? Being president."" #DebateNight",False,2016-09-27T02:01:59,en,51681,102655,"[('trump', 1), ('criticized', 1), ('preparing', 1), ('debate', 1), ('know', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780588035805175808,HillaryClinton,President Obama was born in the United States. He’s American. Trump only has one reason for refusing to admit it. #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T02:01:05,en,6818,17734,"[('president', 1), ('obama', 1), ('born', 1), ('united', 1), ('state', 1)]","[('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
780587655109181440,HillaryClinton,"Still a complete lie. #DebateNight 
https://t.co/F8aCfIqYWs",False,2016-09-27T01:59:34,en,4564,7201,"[('still', 1), ('complete', 1), ('lie', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('#DebateNight \r\n', 'MONEY'), ('https://t.co/F8aCfIqYWs', 'PERSON')]"
780586814126034945,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump is more concerned with pandering to the gun lobby than keeping families safe. #DebateNight https://t.co/LspcUJNUc5,False,2016-09-27T01:56:13,en,7324,13832,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('concerned', 1), ('pandering', 1), ('gun', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780586553836003333,HillaryClinton,"The fact that Trump's answer to a question about racial injustice is just ""we need law and order"" pretty much says it all. #debatenight",False,2016-09-27T01:55:11,en,10882,21951,"[('fact', 1), ('trump', 1), ('answer', 1), ('question', 1), ('racial', 1)]","[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780586416476676098,HillaryClinton,We’ve got to address the systemic racism in our criminal justice system and end private prisons. #DebateNight https://t.co/8afCXJAAjI,False,2016-09-27T01:54:38,en,2587,6006,"[('got', 1), ('address', 1), ('systemic', 1), ('racism', 1), ('criminal', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'ORG')]"
780585761309659136,HillaryClinton,How Hillary Clinton Took Charge In The First Presidential Debate https://t.co/4gwtCnACV0,True,2016-09-27T01:52:02,en,1259,2676,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('took', 1), ('charge', 1), ('first', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
780585423764647936,HillaryClinton,We are not going to bring New York’s unconstitutional stop-and-frisk program nationwide. #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T01:50:42,en,6923,17156,"[('going', 1), ('bring', 1), ('new', 1), ('york', 1), ('unconstitutional', 1)]","[('New York’s', 'GPE')]"
780583951647768577,HillaryClinton,"""Maybe he didn't do a good job."" —Donald Trump

Looks like you “loved” it at the time. #DebateNight… https://t.co/LelC6Tb3nj",False,2016-09-27T01:44:51,en,4435,8347,"[('maybe', 1), ('good', 1), ('job', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780582940732424192,HillaryClinton,"""It's about time this country had somebody running it who has an idea about money."" —Trump #debatenight https://t.co/dpDrKCHVCd",False,2016-09-27T01:40:50,en,2469,5868,"[('time', 1), ('country', 1), ('somebody', 1), ('running', 1), ('idea', 1)]",[]
780582541019475968,HillaryClinton,"Paying zero in taxes doesn’t make you ""smart.""

It makes you a tax evader. https://t.co/g9nQkSRvTB",False,2016-09-27T01:39:14,en,20195,33668,"[('tax', 2), ('make', 2), ('paying', 1), ('zero', 1), ('smart', 1)]","[('zero', 'CARDINAL')]"
780582086231126016,HillaryClinton,No wonder Donald Trump is hiding his tax returns. #debatenight https://t.co/gcvsadMwHJ,False,2016-09-27T01:37:26,en,8568,15157,"[('wonder', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('hiding', 1), ('tax', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780581355633700864,HillaryClinton,"No legit reason @realDonaldTrump can't release returns while being audited, but if scared, release earlier returns no longer under audit.",True,2016-09-27T01:34:32,en,11973,15567,"[('release', 2), ('return', 2), ('legit', 1), ('reason', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1)]",[]
780579726389809152,HillaryClinton,"In the spirit of friendship, here's Donald Trump's ISIS plan for your consideration. #debate https://t.co/YCXFWZyiGA",True,2016-09-27T01:28:03,en,4128,5914,"[('spirit', 1), ('friendship', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('isi', 1)]","[(""Donald Trump's"", 'PERSON'), ('ISIS', 'ORG'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
780579514938261504,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump may live in his own reality—but we've got his own words right here. Check them out: https://t.co/NLPH8sbAGn #debatenight,False,2016-09-27T01:27:13,en,5904,8292,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('may', 1), ('live', 1), ('reality', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780578052216676352,HillaryClinton,"We can step up and confront climate change, save our planet, and invest in clean energy. 

Or, we can do nothing.… https://t.co/U29h8UaYZP",False,2016-09-27T01:21:24,en,2751,6025,"[('step', 1), ('confront', 1), ('climate', 1), ('change', 1), ('save', 1)]",[]
780577643456565248,HillaryClinton,"""I never said that."" —Donald Trump, who said that. #debatenight https://t.co/6T8qV2HCbL",False,2016-09-27T01:19:47,en,91670,134808,"[('said', 2), ('never', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('debatenight', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780577456080166912,HillaryClinton,"""That's called business."" —Donald Trump on the housing crash.

For millions of Americans it was called ""losing their home."" #DebateNight",False,2016-09-27T01:19:02,en,12980,20267,"[('called', 2), ('business', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('housing', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780577128005963776,HillaryClinton,"Economists project that Trump’s plans would add more than $5,000,000,000,000 to the national debt. That's ""trillion"" with a ""T.""",False,2016-09-27T01:17:44,en,3322,6308,"[('economist', 1), ('project', 1), ('trump', 1), ('plan', 1), ('would', 1)]","[('Trump’s', 'ORG'), ('more than $5,000,000,000,000', 'MONEY')]"
780576756713549824,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump seems to think $15 million is a ""small loan."" #debate https://t.co/Bo3HOhdR92 https://t.co/K5bCPX3ujx",True,2016-09-27T01:16:15,en,1738,2478,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('seems', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('$15 million', 'MONEY'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]"
780576523040489472,HillaryClinton,"Every time Trump makes a show of railing against outsourcing, remember the countries he shipped jobs and profits to: https://t.co/5MZTsOgYR9",False,2016-09-27T01:15:20,en,3721,5734,"[('every', 1), ('time', 1), ('trump', 1), ('make', 1), ('show', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
780576124023762944,HillaryClinton,"Having a small business owner for a dad may not get you multi-million-dollar bailouts, but it does teach you the va… https://t.co/3LV3pmjRBI",False,2016-09-27T01:13:45,en,2537,9180,"[('small', 1), ('business', 1), ('owner', 1), ('dad', 1), ('may', 1)]",[]
780575993593524224,HillaryClinton,How many Trump products were made overseas? Here’s the complete list. https://t.co/OdJOZeZau0,True,2016-09-27T01:13:13,en,1656,1563,"[('many', 1), ('trump', 1), ('product', 1), ('made', 1), ('overseas', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
780575611085582336,HillaryClinton,There's only one candidate on stage who will support working families. #DebateNight https://t.co/uOV7JC9uQC,False,2016-09-27T01:11:42,en,3732,7138,"[('one', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('stage', 1), ('support', 1), ('working', 1)]","[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780575331996532737,HillaryClinton,"We have to build an economy that works for everyone, not just those at the top. #DebateNight https://t.co/XPTvh4Dovf",False,2016-09-27T01:10:36,en,2745,6299,"[('build', 1), ('economy', 1), ('work', 1), ('everyone', 1), ('top', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780573935582707712,HillaryClinton,Watch live: Hillary takes the stage for the first presidential debate → https://t.co/FbmDLQp03w #DebateNight,False,2016-09-27T01:05:03,en,804,2137,"[('watch', 1), ('live', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('take', 1), ('stage', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780570465681235968,HillaryClinton,Let's do this. #DebateNight https://t.co/NkPEGHzucT,False,2016-09-27T00:51:15,en,24233,78491,"[('let', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('nkpeghzuct', 1)]","[('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780565409623924736,HillaryClinton,"If you're with Hillary, now's the time to show it. Chip in before tonight's debate to have her back: https://t.co/OftmbqRvyQ #DebateNight",False,2016-09-27T00:31:10,en,1293,4038,"[('hillary', 1), ('time', 1), ('show', 1), ('chip', 1), ('tonight', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('DebateNight', 'PRODUCT')]"
780557354748129280,HillaryClinton,"No matter what Donald says at tonight's debate, we already know the real Trump.

Follow @TheBriefing2016 for the fa… https://t.co/ueK4tWWMN0",False,2016-09-26T23:59:10,en,6014,11459,"[('matter', 1), ('donald', 1), ('say', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('debate', 1)]","[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('Follow @TheBriefing2016', 'PERSON')]"
780551112386633728,HillaryClinton,"Hillary’s set to take the debate stage at 9pm ET.

Here's where you can watch: https://t.co/DhwVYhlA6K #DebateNight https://t.co/gMJINu5xJi",False,2016-09-26T23:34:21,en,1231,3435,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('hillary', 1), ('set', 1), ('take', 1)]","[('9pm ET', 'TIME'), ('DebateNight https://t.co/gMJINu5xJi', 'PRODUCT')]"
780540877047341057,HillaryClinton,"“You didn’t blame Little John or Meat Loaf. You fired Gary Busey.

These are the kinds of decisions that would keep… https://t.co/RT0cARwsu7",False,2016-09-26T22:53:41,en,5463,12162,"[('blame', 1), ('little', 1), ('john', 1), ('meat', 1), ('loaf', 1)]","[('Little John', 'PERSON'), ('Gary Busey', 'PERSON')]"
780528788102864896,HillaryClinton,Study: Donald Trump would raise taxes on millions of middle-class families https://t.co/NmTl8m1R1G https://t.co/INemC8Roms,True,2016-09-26T22:05:39,en,1505,1763,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('study', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
780527183030849536,HillaryClinton,Here are 35 questions Trump still needs to answer. https://t.co/rdMYbHGhwA #DebateNight,False,2016-09-26T21:59:16,en,1747,2989,"[('question', 1), ('trump', 1), ('still', 1), ('need', 1), ('answer', 1)]","[('35', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780504737980485632,HillaryClinton,Watch this before you watch tonight's debate. #DebateNight https://t.co/vnC4bMrS0Q,False,2016-09-26T20:30:05,en,5088,9479,"[('watch', 2), ('tonight', 1), ('debate', 1), ('debatenight', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780495540521955329,HillaryClinton,"Trump told 31 outright lies just last week.

Keep him honest at tonight's debate: Follow @TheBriefing2016 to get th… https://t.co/m1WyJ3DJqF",False,2016-09-26T19:53:32,en,10152,18575,"[('trump', 1), ('told', 1), ('outright', 1), ('lie', 1), ('last', 1)]","[('31', 'CARDINAL'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780485304276881412,HillaryClinton,"""Our presidents are role models for generations of our children. Is this the example we want for them?"" —@NYTimes… https://t.co/lQRruBpQfB",False,2016-09-26T19:12:51,en,1607,3601,"[('president', 1), ('role', 1), ('model', 1), ('generation', 1), ('child', 1)]",[]
780472397694693376,HillaryClinton,Hillary Clinton has a $10 billion plan to stop the heroin epidemic. Donald Trump has some slogans. https://t.co/tN8jGGWrvn,True,2016-09-26T18:21:34,en,1218,2365,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('billion', 1), ('plan', 1), ('stop', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('$10 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780468127322738688,HillaryClinton,"These headlines on Trump's lies are from just one week of his campaign.

Imagine four years of his presidency. https://t.co/FE1hZ7MmR6",False,2016-09-26T18:04:36,en,3653,6195,"[('headline', 1), ('trump', 1), ('lie', 1), ('one', 1), ('week', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('just one week', 'DATE'), ('four years', 'DATE')]"
780461537932771328,HillaryClinton,Everything you need to know before watching tonight's debate: https://t.co/Z4gcpSDfZa https://t.co/bymTtB2Et7,False,2016-09-26T17:38:25,en,2070,3514,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('everything', 1), ('need', 1), ('know', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780446051992043521,HillaryClinton,"Tonight, Hillary will debate Trump for the first time. Follow @TheBriefing2016 to make sure he's held accountable to the facts. #DebateNight",False,2016-09-26T16:36:53,en,2967,6929,"[('tonight', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('debate', 1), ('trump', 1), ('first', 1)]","[('Tonight', 'TIME'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780439472009801728,HillaryClinton,A reminder heading into tonight's debate. #DebateNight https://t.co/TwsbBNPOZP,False,2016-09-26T16:10:44,en,4144,8868,"[('reminder', 1), ('heading', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('debate', 1), ('debatenight', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780431767710928897,HillaryClinton,"""Donald Trump is a man who dwells in bigotry, bluster and false promises."" —@NYTimes https://t.co/dGBX93R3PK #DebateNight",False,2016-09-26T15:40:07,en,2638,5098,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('man', 1), ('dwells', 1), ('bigotry', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('@NYTimes', 'PERSON'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780427115325980672,HillaryClinton,"This job takes maturity, compassion, and wisdom. Only one candidate has what it takes. #DebateNight https://t.co/TAA1qZUdtq",True,2016-09-26T15:21:38,en,2967,7022,"[('take', 2), ('job', 1), ('maturity', 1), ('compassion', 1), ('wisdom', 1)]","[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('DebateNight', 'MONEY')]"
780414643516780544,HillaryClinton,Our daughters deserve better. https://t.co/LJPlFegSTs,False,2016-09-26T14:32:05,en,7164,14549,"[('daughter', 1), ('deserve', 1), ('better', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]",[]
780394697068048384,HillaryClinton,Not a single living president has endorsed Donald Trump. https://t.co/nGXxXTo3NI,False,2016-09-26T13:12:49,en,5330,9552,"[('single', 1), ('living', 1), ('president', 1), ('endorsed', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780386445844422656,HillaryClinton,Trump can't win tonight's debate by lying to the American people. https://t.co/uRkyip3Rfe,False,2016-09-26T12:40:02,en,6678,11110,"[('trump', 1), ('win', 1), ('tonight', 1), ('debate', 1), ('lying', 1)]","[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
780377725328625664,HillaryClinton,RT this if you've got Hillary's back tonight. #Debates2016 https://t.co/r66XZWiNJL,False,2016-09-26T12:05:23,en,28185,29457,"[('rt', 1), ('got', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('back', 1), ('tonight', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
780214115088240640,HillaryClinton,"When we come together, there's no problem we can't solve and no divide we can't heal. https://t.co/2eutCA4R6C",False,2016-09-26T01:15:15,en,3467,8058,"[('come', 1), ('together', 1), ('problem', 1), ('solve', 1), ('divide', 1)]",[]
780207878229598208,HillaryClinton,"Today, the sacrifices of Gold Star families weigh heavier on my mind. Thank you. I will fight to get you the care &amp; benefits you deserve. -H",False,2016-09-26T00:50:28,en,2619,9128,"[('today', 1), ('sacrifice', 1), ('gold', 1), ('star', 1), ('family', 1)]","[('Today', 'DATE'), ('Gold Star', 'ORG')]"
780169819379343364,HillaryClinton,"59 years ago, 9 brave students integrated Central High School, changing the course of history. Let's recommit to fi… https://t.co/wzF4WRU5IS",False,2016-09-25T22:19:14,en,6422,18298,"[('year', 1), ('ago', 1), ('brave', 1), ('student', 1), ('integrated', 1)]","[('59 years ago', 'DATE'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Central High School', 'ORG')]"
780167921746210816,HillaryClinton,Let's send Donald Trump—and the world—a clear message. https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm #LoveTrumpsHate https://t.co/0VI8zmXgZE,False,2016-09-25T22:11:42,en,3904,8583,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('let', 1), ('send', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780152733240135681,HillaryClinton,Imagine Donald Trump sitting in the Situation Room making life or death decisions on behalf of the United States. https://t.co/YFraVXr5Zf,False,2016-09-25T21:11:20,en,10237,16475,"[('imagine', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('sitting', 1), ('situation', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the Situation Room', 'FAC'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
780149449171603456,HillaryClinton,The NYT Editorial Board says Donald Trump should not be president. Here's why. https://t.co/aQ0NZm19Hx via @nytopinion,True,2016-09-25T20:58:17,en,4288,5959,"[('nyt', 1), ('editorial', 1), ('board', 1), ('say', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('NYT', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780146068990357508,HillaryClinton,Take it from those who have been there - Trump is not ready for the responsibility of being president: https://t.co/MCmcwcOwju,True,2016-09-25T20:44:51,en,7563,12670,"[('take', 1), ('trump', 1), ('ready', 1), ('responsibility', 1), ('president', 1)]",[]
780133767063146497,HillaryClinton,"""[Hillary] is one of the most qualified people ever to run for the office, and she easily earns our endorsement.”… https://t.co/AhBE0UuJPO",False,2016-09-25T19:55:58,en,2735,6706,"[('hillary', 1), ('one', 1), ('qualified', 1), ('people', 1), ('ever', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
780122716338651136,HillaryClinton,Our veterans and their families deserve a president who doesn't disrespect and disparage their sacrifices. https://t.co/sMGa9bxZGX,False,2016-09-25T19:12:04,en,3927,8328,"[('veteran', 1), ('family', 1), ('deserve', 1), ('president', 1), ('disrespect', 1)]","[('https://t.co/sMGa9bxZGX', 'PERSON')]"
780107005793071104,HillaryClinton,7 ways Hillary's policies would help you in your daily life: https://t.co/f7oDXlVyx6,False,2016-09-25T18:09:38,en,1563,3129,"[('way', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('policy', 1), ('would', 1), ('help', 1)]","[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('daily', 'DATE')]"
780094699264770048,HillaryClinton,This war hero's Gold Star parents want you to know why they're backing .@HillaryClinton for president… https://t.co/6vEh87N02B,True,2016-09-25T17:20:44,en,1516,2897,"[('war', 1), ('hero', 1), ('gold', 1), ('star', 1), ('parent', 1)]","[('Gold Star', 'ORG')]"
780088306314928128,HillaryClinton,"Once again, Trump's own words are the best evidence he's not fit to be president. https://t.co/D3Ox56zt1k",True,2016-09-25T16:55:20,en,2620,4385,"[('trump', 1), ('word', 1), ('best', 1), ('evidence', 1), ('fit', 1)]","[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780081425714335747,HillaryClinton,Gold Star families have made sacrifices most of us can't even fathom. They deserve our respect and our thanks. https://t.co/c9gDHudBjt,False,2016-09-25T16:27:59,en,3281,8593,"[('gold', 1), ('star', 1), ('family', 1), ('made', 1), ('sacrifice', 1)]","[('Gold Star', 'ORG')]"
780064257631289344,HillaryClinton,Not one living president has said they believe Donald Trump has what it takes to be Commander-in-Chief. https://t.co/3HeTtkQ6KS,False,2016-09-25T15:19:46,en,7952,14148,"[('one', 1), ('living', 1), ('president', 1), ('said', 1), ('believe', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
780047067389517824,HillaryClinton,Meet three women who inspired Hillary to become the person she is today: https://t.co/1O4rw3ecBH https://t.co/Df9X0o5E6h,False,2016-09-25T14:11:28,en,1765,5867,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('meet', 1), ('three', 1), ('woman', 1)]","[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
780030623247392768,HillaryClinton,"""Our endorsement is rooted in respect for her intellect, experience, toughness and courage."" —@NYTimes on Hillary… https://t.co/ihdRZdqGva",False,2016-09-25T13:06:07,en,3246,7907,"[('endorsement', 1), ('rooted', 1), ('respect', 1), ('intellect', 1), ('experience', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/ihdRZdqGva', 'GPE')]"
779830115643617280,HillaryClinton,"The new @NMAAHC is an overdue tribute to African American history. Let's build a more open, inclusive future by reflecting on our past. -H",False,2016-09-24T23:49:22,en,3487,11181,"[('new', 1), ('nmaahc', 1), ('overdue', 1), ('tribute', 1), ('african', 1)]","[('@NMAAHC', 'ORG'), ('African American', 'NORP')]"
779817238346002432,HillaryClinton,"""Our choice, Hillary Clinton, has a record of service and a raft of pragmatic ideas."" —@NYTimes endorsing Hillary… https://t.co/7Sus2PxlWC",False,2016-09-24T22:58:12,en,2314,5977,"[('hillary', 2), ('choice', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('record', 1), ('service', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779801578723217408,HillaryClinton,"""I thought, this woman—I want to ride with her."" —Roxie, a Republican and small business owner, on meeting Hillary https://t.co/s5zyaOBLXB",False,2016-09-24T21:55:59,en,4796,11582,"[('thought', 1), ('woman', 1), ('want', 1), ('ride', 1), ('roxie', 1)]","[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779788945953591296,HillaryClinton,Hillary's been fighting for women and girls her entire career—and she's just getting started. https://t.co/NMnrgEzNkT,False,2016-09-24T21:05:47,en,3063,7546,"[('hillary', 1), ('fighting', 1), ('woman', 1), ('girl', 1), ('entire', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779767715040989184,HillaryClinton,"""A lifetime’s commitment to solving problems in the real world qualifies Hillary Clinton for this job."" —@NYTimes https://t.co/qaswl7IOOJ",False,2016-09-24T19:41:25,en,3454,8113,"[('lifetime', 1), ('commitment', 1), ('solving', 1), ('problem', 1), ('real', 1)]","[('lifetime', 'DATE'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
779756206231617536,HillaryClinton,We know all too well who Donald Trump is. Let's make sure he never becomes president: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/3lJjQEQ0BR,False,2016-09-24T18:55:41,en,4003,9250,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('know', 1), ('well', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779734296160530432,HillaryClinton,"RT if you believe that #LoveTrumpsHate

Then make sure you're registered to vote: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/TlXODnaV53",False,2016-09-24T17:28:37,en,5254,7252,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('rt', 1), ('believe', 1), ('lovetrumpshate', 1)]","[('RT', 'ORG')]"
779714455525556224,HillaryClinton,The NYT Editorial Board endorses Hillary Clinton for president https://t.co/aSQ7lkaR6w via @nytopinion https://t.co/Zm4O1AcVS2,True,2016-09-24T16:09:47,en,4585,8232,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('nyt', 1), ('editorial', 1), ('board', 1)]","[('NYT', 'ORG'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
779703224458743808,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump doesn't see people like Anastasia—he only sees disability. https://t.co/0aDgpwHtjv,False,2016-09-24T15:25:09,en,3907,8181,"[('see', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('people', 1), ('like', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Anastasia', 'GPE')]"
779502695187148800,HillaryClinton,"""Hillary Clinton is one of the best prepared candidates to seek the presidency."" —@LATimes https://t.co/NG1am536OS",False,2016-09-24T02:08:19,en,3025,7505,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('one', 1), ('best', 1), ('prepared', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
779485052216471552,HillaryClinton,Tell a girl to run - for office! #DeclareYourAmbition at https://t.co/Gcthrb8QwO https://t.co/AAIOYi1hFA,True,2016-09-24T00:58:13,en,1464,2652,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('tell', 1), ('girl', 1), ('run', 1)]",[]
779473882910720000,HillaryClinton,"If the young women of this country have Donald Trump as their president, what will they think of themselves? https://t.co/1IrjWddzzy",False,2016-09-24T00:13:50,en,14240,24144,"[('young', 1), ('woman', 1), ('country', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779464482984697856,HillaryClinton,Republicans are once again turning their backs on the people of Flint who have waited far too long for help. It's w… https://t.co/sYyqDHAVXp,False,2016-09-23T23:36:29,en,5251,8284,"[('republican', 1), ('turning', 1), ('back', 1), ('people', 1), ('flint', 1)]","[('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Flint', 'GPE')]"
779455891586314240,HillaryClinton,"""I was just blown away by this 9-year-old girl."" —Hillary on meeting disability rights advocate @AnastasiaSomoza https://t.co/nrjcqfGiRe",False,2016-09-23T23:02:20,en,1415,4139,"[('blown', 1), ('away', 1), ('year', 1), ('old', 1), ('girl', 1)]","[('9-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779453173610213376,HillaryClinton,"I wouldn't tolerate anyone talking to my daughter like that, and she wouldn't either. https://t.co/ZExu0ZacWS",True,2016-09-23T22:51:32,en,10548,19228,"[('tolerate', 1), ('anyone', 1), ('talking', 1), ('daughter', 1), ('like', 1)]",[]
779445994987610112,HillaryClinton,"""Donald Trump committed perjury. Or he looked into the faces of the Republican faithful and knowingly lied."" https://t.co/enl4NTjdX4",False,2016-09-23T22:23:01,en,4617,6886,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('committed', 1), ('perjury', 1), ('looked', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP')]"
779428731228196864,HillaryClinton,"The Enquirer editorial board is endorsing Hillary Clinton for president, breaking a nearly century-long tradition of endorsing Republicans.",True,2016-09-23T21:14:25,en,3141,5148,"[('endorsing', 2), ('enquirer', 1), ('editorial', 1), ('board', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Enquirer', 'ORG'), ('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
779424632168411136,HillaryClinton,"""Hillary Clinton would make a sober, smart and pragmatic president. Donald Trump would be a catastrophe."" —@LATimes https://t.co/NG1am536OS",False,2016-09-23T20:58:07,en,3011,7104,"[('would', 2), ('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('make', 1), ('sober', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779409689876566016,HillaryClinton,I’ve released 9 years of tax returns. RT if you agree it’s time for Donald Trump to release his! https://t.co/08whtFVC0r,True,2016-09-23T19:58:45,en,8721,7853,"[('released', 1), ('year', 1), ('tax', 1), ('return', 1), ('rt', 1)]","[('9 years', 'DATE'), ('RT', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779399176564113408,HillaryClinton,Addiction is a disease—not a moral failing. We should support those who are struggling with it. #OpioidAwarenessWeek https://t.co/V9Uz3jVEjN,False,2016-09-23T19:16:58,en,2116,5353,"[('addiction', 1), ('disease', 1), ('moral', 1), ('failing', 1), ('support', 1)]",[]
779390581369864192,HillaryClinton,Charlotte should release police video of the Keith Lamont Scott shooting without delay. We must ensure justice &amp; work to bridge divides. -H,False,2016-09-23T18:42:49,en,9261,20525,"[('charlotte', 1), ('release', 1), ('police', 1), ('video', 1), ('keith', 1)]","[('Charlotte', 'GPE'), ('Lamont Scott', 'PERSON')]"
779362039839887360,HillaryClinton,"""She gives us hope for the future. She's our girl.""  —Roxie, co-owner of @MercersDairy, on Hillary https://t.co/s5zyaOBLXB",False,2016-09-23T16:49:24,en,2289,5976,"[('co', 2), ('give', 1), ('u', 1), ('hope', 1), ('future', 1)]","[('@MercersDairy', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779335288283947008,HillaryClinton,Every Voice is proud to endorse @HillaryClinton for president. https://t.co/S30v1eZtCm https://t.co/2YUAG4wPJu,True,2016-09-23T15:03:06,en,1165,2521,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('every', 1), ('voice', 1), ('proud', 1)]","[('Every Voice', 'ORG')]"
779320180891615232,HillaryClinton,"When Donald Trump speaks about women, our daughters can hear him. https://t.co/0r1N6R8rV6",False,2016-09-23T14:03:04,en,15681,24865,"[('r', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('speaks', 1), ('woman', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779311437663600641,HillaryClinton,"Editorial board: Clinton would be a smart, pragmatic president. Trump would be a catastrophe.… https://t.co/GVsU7ogGPO",True,2016-09-23T13:28:20,en,4876,7833,"[('would', 2), ('editorial', 1), ('board', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('smart', 1)]","[('Editorial', 'ORG'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
779288660067823616,HillaryClinton,Is this the president we want for our daughters? https://t.co/GP4rfhPDGm,False,2016-09-23T11:57:49,en,25177,36223,"[('president', 1), ('want', 1), ('daughter', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1)]",[]
779153070118752256,HillaryClinton,"""He's 70 years old, and he's still a bully."" —Karen on @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/XBCJ4mTj24",False,2016-09-23T02:59:02,en,3712,7486,"[('year', 1), ('old', 1), ('still', 1), ('bully', 1), ('karen', 1)]","[('70 years old', 'DATE')]"
779145074831663105,HillaryClinton,Our favorite moments from Hillary's appearance on Between Two Ferns → https://t.co/tXLPQtR7tb https://t.co/Er2YqHQVhl,False,2016-09-23T02:27:16,en,1974,7091,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('favorite', 1), ('moment', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Between Two Ferns', 'CARDINAL')]"
779106750133837824,HillaryClinton,"""I really regret doing this."" —Hillary on Between Two Ferns https://t.co/OmDyINNCrW",False,2016-09-22T23:54:58,en,14482,37211,"[('really', 1), ('regret', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('two', 1), ('fern', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
779094002805182464,HillaryClinton,Let's make sure nobody who works full-time in America has to live in poverty. https://t.co/mpGBCNlemA https://t.co/fCcXd1MrTo,False,2016-09-22T23:04:19,en,2288,5812,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('let', 1), ('make', 1), ('sure', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE')]"
779066671067762692,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump's ties to Russia may conflict with America's interests—but they're great for his bottom line. https://t.co/gYbm5HxfxG,False,2016-09-22T21:15:43,en,2651,4329,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('tie', 1), ('russia', 1), ('may', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
779058340315951104,HillaryClinton,Very concerned about the outage in Puerto Rico and the millions of families who don't have power. Hoping it's resto… https://t.co/Y2oG1CS2AN,False,2016-09-22T20:42:37,en,2135,5209,"[('concerned', 1), ('outage', 1), ('puerto', 1), ('rico', 1), ('million', 1)]","[('Puerto Rico', 'GPE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
779055195607166977,HillaryClinton,The man who could be your next president may be deeply indebted to another country. Do you trust him to run ours? https://t.co/5TU9olTqd5,False,2016-09-22T20:30:07,en,7764,10957,"[('man', 1), ('could', 1), ('next', 1), ('president', 1), ('may', 1)]",[]
779038725128855552,HillaryClinton,"Most people who are bullies grow out of it. 

Donald Trump hasn't. https://t.co/tEJ9ATm9BS",False,2016-09-22T19:24:40,en,4084,8048,"[('people', 1), ('bully', 1), ('grow', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779016565475962882,HillaryClinton,"""Donald Trump doesn't see people like me, he only sees disability. I honestly feel bad for someone with so much hat… https://t.co/NTeF9u8JpN",False,2016-09-22T17:56:37,en,5362,11359,"[('see', 2), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('people', 1), ('like', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
779006874708475904,HillaryClinton,"""I think this is the most important election in my lifetime."" @ChelseaClinton takes the 🎤 in this week's podcast: https://t.co/dAwaE8Dg0C",False,2016-09-22T17:18:06,en,909,2629,"[('think', 1), ('important', 1), ('election', 1), ('lifetime', 1), ('chelseaclinton', 1)]","[('@ChelseaClinton', 'PERSON'), ('the 🎤 in', 'DATE'), ('week', 'DATE')]"
778985572215955456,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump is really good at spending other people's money—on:

Legal settlements.
Payoffs.
Portraits of himself. https://t.co/C5bXw5brI9",False,2016-09-22T15:53:27,en,7115,12523,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('really', 1), ('good', 1), ('spending', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Payoffs', 'PERSON')]"
778976591770714112,HillaryClinton,Holding back tears right now. For those of us that didn't grow up with #ADA this is amazing. #imwithher #CripTheVote,True,2016-09-22T15:17:46,en,452,1293,"[('holding', 1), ('back', 1), ('tear', 1), ('right', 1), ('u', 1)]","[('ADA', 'ORG')]"
778957908990189568,HillaryClinton,.@HillaryClinton sits down Between Two Ferns with Zach Galifianakis for her most memorable interview yet. https://t.co/169e3KxEyE,True,2016-09-22T14:03:32,en,28387,45833,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('sits', 1), ('two', 1), ('fern', 1), ('zach', 1)]","[('Between Two Ferns', 'CARDINAL'), ('Zach Galifianakis', 'PERSON')]"
778772872659628033,HillaryClinton,Trump should have to answer exactly why he refuses to believe that @POTUS is American. https://t.co/NReJ3wJE8l,False,2016-09-22T01:48:16,en,3652,7127,"[('trump', 1), ('answer', 1), ('exactly', 1), ('refuse', 1), ('believe', 1)]","[('@POTUS', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
778765262933880832,HillaryClinton,Trump mocks people with disabilities. Hillary Clinton wants to expand their job opportunities https://t.co/GuuwvJgwER,True,2016-09-22T01:18:02,en,1572,3188,"[('trump', 1), ('mock', 1), ('people', 1), ('disability', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
778760862169440256,HillaryClinton,"No child should ever have to grow up in poverty, yet far too many do. We have to do better. Here's how: https://t.co/Qo1RmQDwd6",False,2016-09-22T01:00:32,en,2042,4615,"[('child', 1), ('ever', 1), ('grow', 1), ('poverty', 1), ('yet', 1)]",[]
778755177310486528,HillaryClinton,"""You would think there is almost, like, something wrong."" —Donald Trump on Mitt Romney failing to release his tax r… https://t.co/VzUQByCN2A",False,2016-09-22T00:37:57,en,10154,16287,"[('would', 1), ('think', 1), ('almost', 1), ('like', 1), ('something', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Mitt Romney', 'PERSON')]"
778747606864306176,HillaryClinton,Going to bat for kids who are too often counted out has always been a priority for Hillary. https://t.co/lTxRVn3NBM,False,2016-09-22T00:07:52,en,1504,3724,"[('going', 1), ('bat', 1), ('kid', 1), ('often', 1), ('counted', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778731850302758912,HillaryClinton,".@TimKaine is more than just a great running mate—he's a great guy to have as a friend, too. https://t.co/5WX2qYgUjC",False,2016-09-21T23:05:15,en,1517,4639,"[('great', 2), ('timkaine', 1), ('running', 1), ('mate', 1), ('guy', 1)]",[]
778713373873700864,HillaryClinton,We need a president who sees the best in all of us. https://t.co/vX0Oycto1Q,False,2016-09-21T21:51:50,en,3513,7108,"[('need', 1), ('president', 1), ('see', 1), ('best', 1), ('u', 1)]",[]
778705291168755712,HillaryClinton,"Happy anniversary! 4 years ago today, Romney released his 2011 tax returns (which Trump urged him to do). Where are… https://t.co/Aho8vMnwSP",True,2016-09-21T21:19:43,en,3404,4540,"[('happy', 1), ('anniversary', 1), ('year', 1), ('ago', 1), ('today', 1)]","[('4 years ago', 'DATE'), ('Romney', 'PERSON'), ('2011', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
778682662781227008,HillaryClinton,"A disability shouldn't define your future.

At @ChildDefender, Hillary helped give kids the chance to succeed. https://t.co/jaMcdARYn1",False,2016-09-21T19:49:48,en,1828,4315,"[('disability', 1), ('define', 1), ('future', 1), ('childdefender', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('@ChildDefender', 'GPE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778673342404501504,HillaryClinton,"We believe that everyone has value.
We believe that everyone's created equal.
We believe that love trumps hate.
https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm",False,2016-09-21T19:12:46,en,1261,2603,"[('believe', 3), ('everyone', 2), ('value', 1), ('created', 1), ('equal', 1)]",[]
778672847610839040,HillaryClinton,We'll make our economy and country more welcoming to people with disabilities. We all win when everyone gets to share in America's promise.,False,2016-09-21T19:10:48,en,752,2059,"[('make', 1), ('economy', 1), ('country', 1), ('welcoming', 1), ('people', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE')]"
778672424128811009,HillaryClinton,"The ultimate test of our society is how we treat our fellow human beings, especially those who we have previously left behind.",False,2016-09-21T19:09:07,en,900,1914,"[('ultimate', 1), ('test', 1), ('society', 1), ('treat', 1), ('fellow', 1)]",[]
778671551298297856,HillaryClinton,Americans with disabilities deserve the chance to work alongside those without disabilities—to do the same jobs for the same pay &amp; benefits.,False,2016-09-21T19:05:39,en,703,1577,"[('disability', 2), ('american', 1), ('deserve', 1), ('chance', 1), ('work', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
778671261819994113,HillaryClinton,"We’ve got to build an economy that welcomes people with disabilities, values their work, rewards them fairly, and treats them with respect.",False,2016-09-21T19:04:30,en,687,1492,"[('got', 1), ('build', 1), ('economy', 1), ('welcome', 1), ('people', 1)]",[]
778670985516048384,HillaryClinton,Over 60% of adults with disabilities aren’t in the workplace. We have to fix that. https://t.co/J3Jq21ejtR,False,2016-09-21T19:03:24,en,696,1379,"[('adult', 1), ('disability', 1), ('workplace', 1), ('fix', 1), ('http', 1)]","[('Over 60%', 'PERCENT')]"
778670400830070784,HillaryClinton,The ADA and the notion that workplaces and public spaces belong to everyone was one that Democrats and Republicans could both get behind.,True,2016-09-21T19:01:05,en,478,1444,"[('ada', 1), ('notion', 1), ('workplace', 1), ('public', 1), ('space', 1)]","[('ADA', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
778670110319972353,HillaryClinton,None of us gets through life alone. We all have to look out for each other and lift each other up.,False,2016-09-21T18:59:55,en,869,1852,"[('none', 1), ('u', 1), ('get', 1), ('life', 1), ('alone', 1)]",[]
778669685474811904,HillaryClinton,One of Hillary's first jobs out of law school was to find out why kids with disabilities weren't in school. https://t.co/vPMCYQmbls,True,2016-09-21T18:58:14,en,1075,2031,"[('school', 2), ('one', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('first', 1), ('job', 1)]","[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
778669114063806464,HillaryClinton,"Not that long ago, if you had a disability, it defined your entire life. Basic, essential things that others could do, you couldn’t.",True,2016-09-21T18:55:58,en,501,1468,"[('long', 1), ('ago', 1), ('disability', 1), ('defined', 1), ('entire', 1)]",[]
778668146966335488,HillaryClinton,"It's still legal to pay disabled workers less than the minimum wage and Clinton announces her plan to end that:
https://t.co/vEgIqMkmmg",True,2016-09-21T18:52:07,en,1517,2648,"[('still', 1), ('legal', 1), ('pay', 1), ('disabled', 1), ('worker', 1)]","[('Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
778667640646696960,HillaryClinton,"Building an inclusive economy is another reason we’ve got to break down systemic racism, including under-investment in communities of color.",False,2016-09-21T18:50:07,en,636,1368,"[('building', 1), ('inclusive', 1), ('economy', 1), ('another', 1), ('reason', 1)]",[]
778667376686559232,HillaryClinton,"When we leave people out or write them off, we not only shortchange them and their dreams, we shortchange our country and our future.",False,2016-09-21T18:49:04,en,639,1346,"[('shortchange', 2), ('leave', 1), ('people', 1), ('write', 1), ('dream', 1)]",[]
778666930781691905,HillaryClinton,"In America, every person, no matter what you look like or who you are, should have the chance to go as far as your dreams will take you.",False,2016-09-21T18:47:17,en,718,1514,"[('america', 1), ('every', 1), ('person', 1), ('matter', 1), ('look', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE')]"
778666439540633600,HillaryClinton,"We need to come together to turn the tide, stop violence, build trust, and give all our kids the chance to grow up safe and healthy.",False,2016-09-21T18:45:20,en,697,1429,"[('need', 1), ('come', 1), ('together', 1), ('turn', 1), ('tide', 1)]",[]
778666108853313536,HillaryClinton,We've also seen the targeting of police officers—but so many serve every day with courage and honor and are committed to reform.,False,2016-09-21T18:44:01,en,463,1131,"[('also', 1), ('seen', 1), ('targeting', 1), ('police', 1), ('officer', 1)]",[]
778665779906670592,HillaryClinton,"We have two names to add to a long list of African Americans killed by police officers. It’s unbearable, and it needs to become intolerable.",False,2016-09-21T18:42:43,en,948,1827,"[('two', 1), ('name', 1), ('add', 1), ('long', 1), ('list', 1)]","[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('African Americans', 'NORP')]"
778665476071260160,HillaryClinton,Live from Orlando: Watch Hillary share her plan for building an inclusive economy that helps everyone get ahead → https://t.co/IX06FtcZG8,False,2016-09-21T18:41:31,en,1279,3461,"[('live', 1), ('orlando', 1), ('watch', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('share', 1)]","[('Orlando', 'GPE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778644136954036224,HillaryClinton,Every student should be able to graduate from college without taking on any debt. https://t.co/1aWqDOKh7p https://t.co/KHguTDbKW9,False,2016-09-21T17:16:43,en,2291,5269,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('every', 1), ('student', 1), ('able', 1)]",[]
778604976516001796,HillaryClinton,Keith Lamont Scott. Terence Crutcher. Too many others. This has got to end. -H,False,2016-09-21T14:41:06,en,6170,13075,"[('keith', 1), ('lamont', 1), ('scott', 1), ('terence', 1), ('crutcher', 1)]","[('Keith Lamont Scott', 'PERSON'), ('Terence Crutcher', 'PERSON')]"
778431365884833792,HillaryClinton,"Have student debt? 
Planning for college?
See how much money Hillary's plan would save you:
https://t.co/fiXgr6S3Ye https://t.co/B8PCks6yXL",False,2016-09-21T03:11:14,en,1773,3809,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('student', 1), ('debt', 1), ('planning', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/fiXgr6S3Ye', 'PERSON')]"
778423145648754688,HillaryClinton,FACT: Donald Trump used his charitable foundation to purchase *multiple* six-foot-tall paintings of himself. https://t.co/tDeBH37w7h,False,2016-09-21T02:38:34,en,3824,6359,"[('fact', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('used', 1), ('charitable', 1)]","[('FACT', 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('six-foot', 'QUANTITY')]"
778414941376245760,HillaryClinton,"A real headline about the Republican nominee: ""Trump used $258,000 from his charity to settle legal problems."" https://t.co/2LRtZB3Ri2",False,2016-09-21T02:05:58,en,4765,7113,"[('real', 1), ('headline', 1), ('republican', 1), ('nominee', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('258,000', 'MONEY')]"
778398968225079302,HillaryClinton,"Four months from today, our next president will walk into the Oval Office.

Help make sure it's not Donald Trump: https://t.co/Gxp2QdeIhH",False,2016-09-21T01:02:30,en,3490,9754,"[('four', 1), ('month', 1), ('today', 1), ('next', 1), ('president', 1)]","[('Four months from today', 'DATE'), ('the Oval Office', 'FAC'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
778387742820564992,HillaryClinton,"On this day in 1973, tennis champion Billie Jean King defeated Bobby Riggs in the “Battle of the Sexes.” https://t.co/G06Ol90j1O",False,2016-09-21T00:17:54,en,2785,8993,"[('day', 1), ('tennis', 1), ('champion', 1), ('billie', 1), ('jean', 1)]","[('this day', 'DATE'), ('1973', 'DATE'), ('Billie Jean King', 'PERSON'), ('Bobby Riggs', 'PERSON'), ('Battle of the Sexes', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
778353947241218048,HillaryClinton,"""You can leave this ad muted—there's nothing to hear."" —@NyleDiMarco

https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/QOqcWnw7OJ",False,2016-09-20T22:03:36,en,5468,10208,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('leave', 1), ('ad', 1), ('muted', 1)]",[]
778339633763643392,HillaryClinton,"Help get out the vote for Hillary (plus, get a free sticker when you sign up!): https://t.co/v4rISVHYuG",False,2016-09-20T21:06:44,en,731,1767,"[('get', 2), ('help', 1), ('vote', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('plus', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778330554102079488,HillaryClinton,Trump’s calls to torture and mistreat prisoners go against the very values we are fighting to defend. We’re better than this.,False,2016-09-20T20:30:39,en,3196,9289,"[('trump', 1), ('call', 1), ('torture', 1), ('mistreat', 1), ('prisoner', 1)]","[('Trump’s', 'ORG')]"
778324154269458432,HillaryClinton,Donald hasn't given his own money to the Trump Foundation since 2008—but it's still paying his bills. https://t.co/2LRtZB3Ri2,False,2016-09-20T20:05:13,en,4161,6062,"[('donald', 1), ('given', 1), ('money', 1), ('trump', 1), ('foundation', 1)]","[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('the Trump Foundation', 'ORG'), ('2008', 'DATE')]"
778313305500819456,HillaryClinton,It's time to tell @WellsFargo that Wall Street works for Main Street—not the other way around. https://t.co/mYuTS4qgF4,False,2016-09-20T19:22:07,en,1256,3240,"[('street', 2), ('time', 1), ('tell', 1), ('wellsfargo', 1), ('wall', 1)]","[('@WellsFargo', 'ORG'), ('Main Street', 'FAC')]"
778292079231377408,HillaryClinton,NEW: @realdonaldtrump used more $250K+ from his charity to pay off legal settlements of his for-profit businesses.   https://t.co/Fa1RooYWMT,True,2016-09-20T17:57:46,en,10825,8957,"[('new', 1), ('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('used', 1), ('k', 1), ('charity', 1)]","[('@realdonaldtrump', 'ORG'), ('250K+', 'MONEY')]"
778286389448339457,HillaryClinton,Another unarmed Black man was shot in a police incident. This should be intolerable. We have so much work to do. #TerenceCrutcher -H,False,2016-09-20T17:35:09,en,12204,24955,"[('another', 1), ('unarmed', 1), ('black', 1), ('man', 1), ('shot', 1)]","[('TerenceCrutcher', 'ORG')]"
778272551659147265,HillaryClinton,Donald Trump is using his foundation—funded by other people's money—to settle lawsuits. https://t.co/2LRtZBls9A,False,2016-09-20T16:40:10,en,4074,5684,"[('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('using', 1), ('foundation', 1), ('funded', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
778254419678859265,HillaryClinton,"Trump cannot be trusted with his own charity, but we are supposed to believe he can manage the nation’s treasury? https://t.co/DtX6C7Rftb",True,2016-09-20T15:28:07,en,4292,5681,"[('trump', 1), ('trusted', 1), ('charity', 1), ('supposed', 1), ('believe', 1)]",[]
778251997019537408,HillaryClinton,"""Our identities do not have to be defined by putting someone else down but can be enhanced by lifting someone else up"" —@POTUS at #UNGA",True,2016-09-20T15:18:29,en,2448,4935,"[('someone', 2), ('else', 2), ('identity', 1), ('defined', 1), ('putting', 1)]","[('@POTUS', 'ORG'), ('UNGA', 'ORG')]"
778233084017840128,HillaryClinton,"""The voice of your vote is the greatest voice we have."" —@NyleDiMarco

https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/X3oqEoOYsU",False,2016-09-20T14:03:20,en,6195,13976,"[('voice', 2), ('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('vote', 1), ('greatest', 1)]",[]
778063499956195329,HillaryClinton,"""No one has the right to immigrate to this country."" —Donald Trump during his rally in Florida today

We disagree. https://t.co/9gS9q5vQS9",True,2016-09-20T02:49:28,en,1911,3464,"[('one', 1), ('right', 1), ('immigrate', 1), ('country', 1), ('donald', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
778052507037609984,HillaryClinton,Catch @FallonTonight at 11:35pm ET to see letters from some of Hillary's biggest fans. https://t.co/muVNwgLSRs,False,2016-09-20T02:05:47,en,1681,6207,"[('catch', 1), ('fallontonight', 1), ('pm', 1), ('et', 1), ('see', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
778036983558004736,HillaryClinton,"""You want to give me a good send-off? Go vote.” —Barack Obama: https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/Jqf2jmx3D0",False,2016-09-20T01:04:06,en,5965,11729,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('want', 1), ('give', 1), ('good', 1)]","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON')]"
778023288761180160,HillaryClinton,Nobody in America should have to forgo a higher education because they can't afford it. https://t.co/DhSlyM6ILQ,False,2016-09-20T00:09:41,en,3251,9288,"[('nobody', 1), ('america', 1), ('forgo', 1), ('higher', 1), ('education', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE')]"
778007963009179648,HillaryClinton,Barack Obama said progress is on the ballot this November. This economic data shows he’s right. https://t.co/CIoKKKIxqz,False,2016-09-19T23:08:47,en,1845,4122,"[('barack', 1), ('obama', 1), ('said', 1), ('progress', 1), ('ballot', 1)]","[('Barack Obama', 'PERSON'), ('this November', 'DATE')]"
777998343553290241,HillaryClinton,America has never made progress by thinking one person alone can fix our problems. https://t.co/mYba5FCBrb,False,2016-09-19T22:30:34,en,3562,9311,"[('america', 1), ('never', 1), ('made', 1), ('progress', 1), ('thinking', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
777980962877665284,HillaryClinton,"""Everyone who wants to go to college should be able to without drowning in debt."" —Hillary https://t.co/wDxspmxT9Q",False,2016-09-19T21:21:30,en,1688,4377,"[('everyone', 1), ('want', 1), ('go', 1), ('college', 1), ('able', 1)]",[]
777966037908221952,HillaryClinton,Be a voter. Check your registration and help your friends do the same → https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm https://t.co/yTAG2iT8WL,False,2016-09-19T20:22:12,en,2670,5169,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('voter', 1), ('check', 1), ('registration', 1)]",[]
777952999100522496,HillaryClinton,"When @HillaryClinton says she’s going to make public colleges and universities tuition-free, you know what? That's a very big deal.",True,2016-09-19T19:30:23,en,5661,15689,"[('hillaryclinton', 1), ('say', 1), ('going', 1), ('make', 1), ('public', 1)]","[('@HillaryClinton', 'PERSON')]"
777946240390668288,HillaryClinton,"Let’s make clear that love trumps hate—not just this November, but always. https://t.co/wDxspmxT9Q",False,2016-09-19T19:03:31,en,1625,4275,"[('let', 1), ('make', 1), ('clear', 1), ('love', 1), ('trump', 1)]","[('’s', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE')]"
777936395319009280,HillaryClinton,Find out how much Hillary's college plan will save you: https://t.co/svkSUzhwYz https://t.co/tmHf8m2CdX,False,2016-09-19T18:24:24,en,1006,2007,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('find', 1), ('much', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777917942180773888,HillaryClinton,"""The lesson she passed on to me was simple but powerful: No one gets through life alone."" —Hillary on her mom https://t.co/gzNvfNPeNu",False,2016-09-19T17:11:05,en,1658,4625,"[('lesson', 1), ('passed', 1), ('simple', 1), ('powerful', 1), ('one', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777915454186749952,HillaryClinton,"When we work together, we will trump hate. https://t.co/tTgeqxNqYm",False,2016-09-19T17:01:11,en,783,1958,"[('work', 1), ('together', 1), ('trump', 1), ('hate', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
777914352884146176,HillaryClinton,Go to https://t.co/SvSvlg48vI and register to vote today. Register your friends. Register everyone you know.,True,2016-09-19T16:56:49,en,841,1446,"[('register', 3), ('go', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('svsvlg', 1)]","[('today', 'DATE')]"
777913541445771264,HillaryClinton,"We have to stand up to this hate.

We have to send a clear message: 
America is better than this.
America is better than Donald Trump.",False,2016-09-19T16:53:35,en,2419,5552,"[('america', 2), ('better', 2), ('stand', 1), ('hate', 1), ('send', 1)]","[('America', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
777913311459418112,HillaryClinton,"We're facing a candidate with a history of discrimination in his businesses, who retweets white supremacists, and led the birther movement.",False,2016-09-19T16:52:41,en,1364,2625,"[('facing', 1), ('candidate', 1), ('history', 1), ('discrimination', 1), ('business', 1)]",[]
777913107708600320,HillaryClinton,"In a democracy, if you want to help the greatest number of people, you have to push for reform from both the outside-in and the inside-out.",False,2016-09-19T16:51:52,en,616,1514,"[('democracy', 1), ('want', 1), ('help', 1), ('greatest', 1), ('number', 1)]",[]
777912462335172609,HillaryClinton,"Simply caring is not enough. To drive real progress, you have to change both hearts and laws. https://t.co/oZIm2is1lX",False,2016-09-19T16:49:18,en,821,1558,"[('simply', 1), ('caring', 1), ('enough', 1), ('drive', 1), ('real', 1)]",[]
777911385200230400,HillaryClinton,No one gets through life alone. We have to look out for each other and lift each other up. https://t.co/FEStrnjjOO,True,2016-09-19T16:45:01,en,801,1835,"[('one', 1), ('get', 1), ('life', 1), ('alone', 1), ('look', 1)]",[]
777910791110623232,HillaryClinton,"""No one will work harder to make your life better. I’ll never stop, no matter how tough it gets."" —Hillary https://t.co/TyXrp8PgsW",True,2016-09-19T16:42:40,en,840,1910,"[('one', 1), ('work', 1), ('harder', 1), ('make', 1), ('life', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777910489170972672,HillaryClinton,"When Americans get knocked down, we get right back up again. We refuse to quit—no matter what. 

That’s the spirit we need in this election.",False,2016-09-19T16:41:28,en,725,1754,"[('get', 2), ('american', 1), ('knocked', 1), ('right', 1), ('back', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
777909915268550660,HillaryClinton,We have a Republican nominee for president who incites hatred and violence like we’ve never seen before.,False,2016-09-19T16:39:11,en,961,2102,"[('republican', 1), ('nominee', 1), ('president', 1), ('incites', 1), ('hatred', 1)]","[('Republican', 'NORP')]"
777909432403496960,HillaryClinton,College should be tuition-free for working families and debt-free for everyone: https://t.co/lkOFcHI4Py,False,2016-09-19T16:37:16,en,525,1152,"[('free', 2), ('college', 1), ('tuition', 1), ('working', 1), ('family', 1)]","[('https://t.co/lkOFcHI4Py', 'PERSON')]"
777909201481916416,HillaryClinton,"If you work hard, you should be able to find a good job that pays well and lets you do what you love and make your mark on the world.",False,2016-09-19T16:36:21,en,556,1231,"[('work', 1), ('hard', 1), ('able', 1), ('find', 1), ('good', 1)]",[]
777909084955762688,HillaryClinton,"We can build a cleaner, more resilient electrical grid with enough renewable energy to power every home in the country.",False,2016-09-19T16:35:53,en,571,1197,"[('build', 1), ('cleaner', 1), ('resilient', 1), ('electrical', 1), ('grid', 1)]",[]
777908918970449920,HillaryClinton,"It’s wrong to tear each other down.
It’s wrong to let income inequality get worse.
It’s wrong to put a loose cannon in charge.",False,2016-09-19T16:35:13,en,693,1387,"[('wrong', 3), ('tear', 1), ('let', 1), ('income', 1), ('inequality', 1)]",[]
777908689227354112,HillaryClinton,This election isn’t a reality TV show. It shouldn’t be about birth certificates or name-calling or stunts to get on cable news.,False,2016-09-19T16:34:19,en,746,1498,"[('election', 1), ('reality', 1), ('tv', 1), ('show', 1), ('birth', 1)]",[]
777908063265251328,HillaryClinton,"You want something to vote for, not just against:

Optimism, not resentment.
Answers, not anger.
Ideas, not insults.
Bridges, not walls.",False,2016-09-19T16:31:49,en,1384,2348,"[('want', 1), ('something', 1), ('vote', 1), ('optimism', 1), ('resentment', 1)]","[('Bridges', 'PERSON')]"
777907710205554688,HillaryClinton,"“Your generation is the most inclusive, progressive, and entrepreneurial we’ve ever seen.” —Hillary to students at @TempleUniv",False,2016-09-19T16:30:25,en,571,1284,"[('generation', 1), ('inclusive', 1), ('progressive', 1), ('entrepreneurial', 1), ('ever', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777907223670493184,HillaryClinton,50 days to go. Don't miss Hillary live from @TempleUniv: https://t.co/qg6J7SXrr0,False,2016-09-19T16:28:29,en,874,3226,"[('day', 1), ('go', 1), ('miss', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('live', 1)]","[('50 days', 'DATE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777903138221109248,HillaryClinton,“I’m Hillary Clinton and I’ve always approved this message.” https://t.co/GgDeBBfoUm,False,2016-09-19T16:12:15,en,4758,12037,"[('hillary', 1), ('clinton', 1), ('always', 1), ('approved', 1), ('message', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
777896080080003072,HillaryClinton,"“This threat is real, but so is our resolve. Americans will not cower. We will prevail.” —Hillary https://t.co/eADlIG9aQL",False,2016-09-19T15:44:12,en,1596,4056,"[('threat', 1), ('real', 1), ('resolve', 1), ('american', 1), ('cower', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Hillary https://t.co/eADlIG9aQL', 'PERSON')]"
777889026661556224,HillaryClinton,"Not only is @realDonaldTrump wrong on birtherism, his words and policies are bad for Americans alive now and our children yet to be born.",True,2016-09-19T15:16:11,en,786,1898,"[('realdonaldtrump', 1), ('wrong', 1), ('birtherism', 1), ('word', 1), ('policy', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
777880745939443713,HillaryClinton,Our next president needs to have the right temperament to meet the challenges we face. https://t.co/XMDZPtLNMB,False,2016-09-19T14:43:16,en,2803,7439,"[('next', 1), ('president', 1), ('need', 1), ('right', 1), ('temperament', 1)]",[]
777876269270704128,HillaryClinton,"“What I’ve laid out is a path forward that will keep us safer...and go after the terrorists to finally destroy them"" https://t.co/tWWEMx0T9s",False,2016-09-19T14:25:29,en,590,1615,"[('laid', 1), ('path', 1), ('forward', 1), ('keep', 1), ('u', 1)]",[]
777875261928927232,HillaryClinton,“I’m the only candidate in this race who’s been part of the hard decisions to take terrorists off the battlefield. —Hillary,False,2016-09-19T14:21:29,en,984,2843,"[('candidate', 1), ('race', 1), ('part', 1), ('hard', 1), ('decision', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777873693745811456,HillaryClinton,"""Let us be vigilant, but not afraid…we choose resolve, not fear. We will not turn on each other or undermine each other.” —Hillary",False,2016-09-19T14:15:15,en,1221,2645,"[('let', 1), ('u', 1), ('vigilant', 1), ('afraid', 1), ('choose', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777873205310676992,HillaryClinton,"""Like all Americans, my thoughts are with those who were wounded, their families, &amp; our first responders” —Hillary on this weekend’s attacks",False,2016-09-19T14:13:18,en,1739,6703,"[('like', 1), ('american', 1), ('thought', 1), ('wounded', 1), ('family', 1)]","[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('weekend', 'DATE')]"
777868477310918656,HillaryClinton,"Want to do a small part to help defeat Trump in November? RT this link and get everyone registered, and confirmed. https://t.co/1R7UN7e0a0",True,2016-09-19T13:54:31,en,4478,3625,"[('want', 1), ('small', 1), ('part', 1), ('help', 1), ('defeat', 1)]","[('November', 'DATE')]"
777858612727250948,HillaryClinton,.@HillaryClinton wrote for us about what millennials have taught her during this election: https://t.co/SlMZZ1C19f https://t.co/qNUEzbQeYR,True,2016-09-19T13:15:19,en,1446,2507,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('hillaryclinton', 1), ('wrote', 1), ('u', 1)]",[]
777702286499860480,HillaryClinton,"""We have got to do everything we can to make sure that Hillary Clinton is elected president."" —@BernieSanders https://t.co/t1uxcoVJT5",False,2016-09-19T02:54:08,en,7718,16135,"[('got', 1), ('everything', 1), ('make', 1), ('sure', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary Clinton', 'PERSON')]"
777690030882127872,HillaryClinton,"Grateful for our brave men and women serving in the @USAirForce and their families. Happy birthday, USAF! https://t.co/xYebpm9NaN",False,2016-09-19T02:05:26,en,1575,4785,"[('grateful', 1), ('brave', 1), ('men', 1), ('woman', 1), ('serving', 1)]",[]
777673718982184964,HillaryClinton,"Congratulations on your Emmy, Kate! Big fan of yours, too. https://t.co/w00QO1GwyH",False,2016-09-19T01:00:37,en,15087,50882,"[('congratulation', 1), ('emmy', 1), ('kate', 1), ('big', 1), ('fan', 1)]","[('Kate', 'PERSON')]"
777664718848745473,HillaryClinton,"""Progress is on the ballot.
Tolerance is on the ballot.
Democracy is on the ballot.
Justice is on the ballot."" https://t.co/Mmyqestken",False,2016-09-19T00:24:51,en,13167,25139,"[('ballot', 4), ('progress', 1), ('tolerance', 1), ('democracy', 1), ('justice', 1)]","[('Justice', 'ORG')]"
777650431963107328,HillaryClinton,"Next week, Hillary will walk on stage for the first presidential debate. Chip in now for the chance to be there: https://t.co/mHGncsXG6y",False,2016-09-18T23:28:05,en,1226,4224,"[('next', 1), ('week', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('walk', 1), ('stage', 1)]","[('Next week', 'DATE'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
777642761579270144,HillaryClinton,We've got 51 days left to win this thing. Make sure you're ready: https://t.co/B21QKpeiSj https://t.co/nZTkkuxtDP,True,2016-09-18T22:57:36,en,2642,7182,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('got', 1), ('day', 1), ('left', 1)]","[('51 days', 'DATE')]"
777636788814880770,HillaryClinton,FACT: The @ClintonFdn spends 87% on its life changing work: https://t.co/z0zW4Axdbc https://t.co/GtI94aBp4m,True,2016-09-18T22:33:52,en,1449,2725,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('fact', 1), ('clintonfdn', 1), ('spends', 1)]","[('FACT', 'ORG'), ('87%', 'PERCENT')]"
777630082378690560,HillaryClinton,It wasn't so long ago that women faced and took down barriers that can seem ridiculous now. https://t.co/nuG8Gqmzt1 https://t.co/XwvEuxsrOV,False,2016-09-18T22:07:13,en,4127,6434,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('long', 1), ('ago', 1), ('woman', 1)]",[]
777618304332627968,HillaryClinton,"""I strongly condemn the apparent terrorist attacks in Minnesota, New Jersey, and New York."" https://t.co/NSy3fkcu1c",False,2016-09-18T21:20:25,en,2804,7537,"[('new', 2), ('strongly', 1), ('condemn', 1), ('apparent', 1), ('terrorist', 1)]","[('Minnesota', 'GPE'), ('New Jersey', 'GPE'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
777613325299355648,HillaryClinton,"Joel Sollender, WWII veteran and POW, on what it means when he hears Trump insult our vets. https://t.co/3ZIezeRTl9",False,2016-09-18T21:00:38,en,6443,10886,"[('joel', 1), ('sollender', 1), ('wwii', 1), ('veteran', 1), ('pow', 1)]","[('Joel Sollender', 'PERSON'), ('WWII', 'EVENT')]"
777605055834890242,HillaryClinton,"So, what do the candidates’ foundations do again? https://t.co/PVrx1SeUxs",True,2016-09-18T20:27:47,en,2731,4336,"[('candidate', 1), ('foundation', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('pvrx', 1)]",[]
777578838498873344,HillaryClinton,"When we stand together - as white, black and hispanic, gay and straight, women and men - we trump hate. https://t.co/B8aVUwudDc",True,2016-09-18T18:43:36,en,4515,9680,"[('stand', 1), ('together', 1), ('white', 1), ('black', 1), ('hispanic', 1)]",[]
777573464739688448,HillaryClinton,"""Read up on your history. It matters. We've got to get people to vote."" —@POTUS: https://t.co/tTgeqy51PU https://t.co/GyveEjARku",False,2016-09-18T18:22:15,en,3504,7256,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('read', 1), ('history', 1), ('matter', 1)]",[]
777552290441859072,HillaryClinton,So what exactly is Donald Trump hiding from voters? Pretty much everything. https://t.co/RGUqGN4I7i,False,2016-09-18T16:58:06,en,6413,11141,"[('exactly', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('hiding', 1), ('voter', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('https://t.co/RGUqGN4I7i', 'PERSON')]"
777540558210396160,HillaryClinton,“We have to face the world as it is but commit ourselves to turning it into what it should be.” —Hillary https://t.co/nEB4qSm2YX,False,2016-09-18T16:11:29,en,2254,5721,"[('face', 1), ('world', 1), ('commit', 1), ('turning', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777521877535322112,HillaryClinton,"In a normal election, these 126 things would disqualify Trump from becoming president: https://t.co/VeDJknt4JH",False,2016-09-18T14:57:15,en,3123,5449,"[('normal', 1), ('election', 1), ('thing', 1), ('would', 1), ('disqualify', 1)]","[('126', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
777493990434336768,HillaryClinton,"If you want to go to college or are saddled with student debt, you'll want to read what @TimKaine has to say: https://t.co/qa9qO4AFxW",False,2016-09-18T13:06:27,en,1979,4692,"[('want', 2), ('go', 1), ('college', 1), ('saddled', 1), ('student', 1)]",[]
777316191798980631,HillaryClinton,"As @FLOTUS said, this election is about what kind of country we want to be and what we want to leave behind for future generations.",False,2016-09-18T01:19:56,en,1460,4157,"[('want', 2), ('flotus', 1), ('said', 1), ('election', 1), ('kind', 1)]","[('@FLOTUS', 'ORG')]"
777315864987181056,HillaryClinton,"We need ideas, not insults. Plans, not paranoia.

We can’t let @POTUS's legacy fall into the hands of someone who doesn’t understand that.",False,2016-09-18T01:18:38,en,2026,5121,"[('need', 1), ('idea', 1), ('insult', 1), ('plan', 1), ('paranoia', 1)]","[('@POTUS', 'ORG')]"
777315293936881664,HillaryClinton,"""I’m going to close my campaign the way I began my career…focused on opportunities for children and fairness for families."" —Hillary",False,2016-09-18T01:16:22,en,1225,3266,"[('going', 1), ('close', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('way', 1), ('began', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777314115996020736,HillaryClinton,Tune in now to watch Hillary speak to the @OfficialCBC: https://t.co/NJuB7JkyDL,False,2016-09-18T01:11:41,en,686,2276,"[('tune', 1), ('watch', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('speak', 1), ('officialcbc', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('@OfficialCBC', 'ORG')]"
777301674377478144,HillaryClinton,Presidential. https://t.co/tlfpcbVqkT,False,2016-09-18T00:22:15,en,5091,13118,"[('presidential', 1), ('http', 1), ('co', 1), ('tlfpcbvqkt', 1)]",[]
777294443724496896,HillaryClinton,"This year, Janelle beat breast cancer with the support of her family, friends, and a presidential candidate. https://t.co/vmavvobLcs",False,2016-09-17T23:53:31,en,2335,7156,"[('year', 1), ('janelle', 1), ('beat', 1), ('breast', 1), ('cancer', 1)]","[('This year', 'DATE'), ('Janelle', 'PERSON')]"
777283365355552768,HillaryClinton,"So how exactly did Donald Trump build his own bank account?

On the backs of American taxpayers: https://t.co/4uBuIljQML",False,2016-09-17T23:09:30,en,2926,4794,"[('exactly', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('build', 1), ('bank', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
777276144353705984,HillaryClinton,"""I want you to know that I see you, and I’m with you."" —Hillary to the Latino community at @CHCI https://t.co/t2F93Ml785",False,2016-09-17T22:40:48,en,1636,4340,"[('want', 1), ('know', 1), ('see', 1), ('hillary', 1), ('latino', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Latino', 'ORG'), ('@CHCI', 'ORG')]"
777254015734321152,HillaryClinton,Trump went to Flint to draw attention to the city's lead poisoning crisis—but he just made a spectacle of himself. https://t.co/Dw4KoVgrQ3,False,2016-09-17T21:12:52,en,2384,5635,"[('trump', 1), ('went', 1), ('flint', 1), ('draw', 1), ('attention', 1)]","[('Flint', 'GPE')]"
777233144093310976,HillaryClinton,Let's be clear: Nothing—including an audit—is preventing Trump from releasing his tax returns. https://t.co/mpGiRIaPgD,False,2016-09-17T19:49:56,en,5993,10676,"[('let', 1), ('clear', 1), ('nothing', 1), ('including', 1), ('audit', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
777224189107400704,HillaryClinton,Any of these examples proves that Donald Trump is unfit to be president. https://t.co/3mQgqZ7b8V,False,2016-09-17T19:14:21,en,2216,4195,"[('example', 1), ('prof', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('unfit', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
777215229973426176,HillaryClinton,"""We’re siding with students and with every American seeking an affordable college degree."" —@TimKaine https://t.co/qa9qO4AFxW",False,2016-09-17T18:38:45,en,1411,3836,"[('siding', 1), ('student', 1), ('every', 1), ('american', 1), ('seeking', 1)]","[('American', 'NORP')]"
777195717978910720,HillaryClinton,"When your friends say they won't vote, ask how much student debt they have. There's only one candidate who will make college affordable.",True,2016-09-17T17:21:13,en,5019,11284,"[('friend', 1), ('say', 1), ('vote', 1), ('ask', 1), ('much', 1)]","[('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
777177731536596992,HillaryClinton,"Hillary's been her childhood pen pal, her graduation cheering section, and her friend. Meet Aleatha: https://t.co/f4YzTBmIdl",False,2016-09-17T16:09:45,en,5317,12569,"[('hillary', 1), ('childhood', 1), ('pen', 1), ('pal', 1), ('graduation', 1)]","[('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777164184505114624,HillaryClinton,Take it from @FLOTUS: This election is too important to sit out. Register to vote: https://t.co/tTgeqy51PU https://t.co/NblU3Tth7T,False,2016-09-17T15:15:55,en,4205,9109,"[('http', 2), ('co', 2), ('take', 1), ('flotus', 1), ('election', 1)]","[('@FLOTUS', 'ORG')]"
777144008044847105,HillaryClinton,"9 times Donald Trump accused Hillary of doing the terrible things he, himself, actually did: https://t.co/DXlybx7oA5",False,2016-09-17T13:55:44,en,4541,7331,"[('time', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('accused', 1), ('hillary', 1)]","[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON')]"
777124713575378944,HillaryClinton,It’s time for Donald Trump to be held to the same standard of disclosure as any other major party nominee. https://t.co/UP93LCzURv,False,2016-09-17T12:39:04,en,4734,9240,"[('time', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('held', 1), ('standard', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
776947295896084481,HillaryClinton,It's great to be back on the campaign trail. https://t.co/vm1KX2uOXt,False,2016-09-17T00:54:04,en,2638,13665,"[('great', 1), ('back', 1), ('campaign', 1), ('trail', 1), ('http', 1)]",[]
776932768081031168,HillaryClinton,The brave men and women who have served our country deserve better than Donald Trump. https://t.co/SmLmTrVhOr,False,2016-09-16T23:56:21,en,7874,15940,"[('brave', 1), ('men', 1), ('woman', 1), ('served', 1), ('country', 1)]","[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
776920011789234176,HillaryClinton,126 things Donald Trump has said and done that should disqualify his candidacy: https://t.co/h4qUNNnTOf,False,2016-09-16T23:05:39,en,3784,6186,"[('thing', 1), ('donald', 1), ('trump', 1), ('said', 1), ('done', 1)]","[('126', 'CARDINAL'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
776907829022195713,HillaryClinton,"Trump's habit of projecting his actions onto someone else is what 6-year-olds call ""I know you are, but what am I?"" https://t.co/FIhZYLmy1l",False,2016-09-16T22:17:15,en,3270,6903,"[('trump', 1), ('habit', 1), ('projecting', 1), ('action', 1), ('onto', 1)]","[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('6-year-olds', 'DATE')]"
776898567004839936,HillaryClinton,"Donald Trump has spent years peddling lies about President Obama.
